In the end, who's the person named D?
If she really gave us Wisdom, that could mean she's the admin.
Yes, that's your reward.
If she's the admin in charge of skills...
Then she must have something in mind.
Besides, D speaks Japanese fluently.
And the smartphone appeared.
In other words, we see the shadow of Japan.
That's right.
D, this world and Earth are probably related.
She should know the reason we're reincarnated into this world.
She will not answer even if we ask her.
I want to know!
As the person in charge of information, I'm trying to process all the information.
How am I suppose to work if you keep whining?
I can't process it at all!
Sorry.
But thanks to your nagging, I have an answer!
What?
Which is...
There's no point cracking our head on this.
What?
We should focus on doing things we can,
which is crossing Middle Stratum.
Besides, I've used my skill points to redeem Spatial Magic.
Which is what the man in black used.
I think that skill is useful.
Once Spatial Magic is obtained, we can go upstairs in an instant.
Why didn't you say this earlier?
No...
Because it's tough to cast Spatial Magic.
Are we thinking too simple?
It's as sweet as pouring condensed milk and three buckets of sugar on syrup.
But hold on...
Isn't that the road leading to Upper Stratum?
We don't need Spatial Magic to reach Upper Stratum.
Hooray!
EPISODE 10: WHO IS THIS, GEEZER?
♫Looking at the end of the entangled karma♫
♫Even my back is full of enemies♫
♫Thousand of creatures♫
♫who are arrogant and ready to charge♫
♫Dive for alive♫
♫Climb for life♫
♫A chaotic state that no one can survive♫
♫Take this as my stage♫
♫Is this over?♫
♫But I'm not done♫
♫Even if you didn't see the fatal silk♫
♫you'll be eaten by me if you fall into the web♫
♫Deeper... inside♫
♫Spider pride made a cruel mark♫
♫in this chest again♫
♫Finding the perfect way isn't enough♫
♫The shredded life must be reformed♫
♫Think desperately♫
♫Fight desperately♫
♫The so-called reality. Feel a bit cold♫
♫Keep living the spider way♫
♫Wait and see♫
SO I'M A SPIDER, SO WHAT?
You got the title of Warrior.
You should know what this means, Schlain.
Yes.
Julius...
Leston, brother...
Brother Julius is...
Brother is...
Father, I know you're very sad.
But shouldn't we discuss what we should do next?
Brother Cylis.
Can't you be considerate of father's and Shun's feelings?
No. Cylis is right.
Father.
Schlain got the title of Warrior, that means Julius is dead.
We're the royal.
We must first fulfill our duty.
I didn't expect Julius's successor
to also be one from our country and it's even his brother.
Is this karma as well?
Although the nation is not informed, the league of the Demon Clan is attacking.
Demon Clan?
Julius probably lost his life while fighting them.
To create a world with peace and laughter.
That is the dream I pursue,
until death stops me.
I'm coming in.
The battle situation with the league of Demon Clan has arrived.
Speak up.
Half of the eight fortresses have fallen,
including Kusorion Fortress that has been destroyed.
Kusorion Fortress...
Even the big fortress?
Yes. Because the Queen Taratect appeared, there was no way to fight back.
Julius must have been in Kusorion Fortress.
We don't know where Mr. Julius was.
The rest of the fortresses fought very hard to fend off Demon Clan.
There's only one place,
Dazarro Fortress commanded by Elder Ronandt had a total victory against the enemy.
I see.
Elder Ronandt...
He's known as the strongest wizard among humans, right?
Yes. He's also the master of Brother Julius.
The league of Demon Clan is retreating.
Report complete.
Thank you.
Father.
Do not publish Julius' death and Schlain's new title yet.
If we announce the death of Warrior hastily, the folks may be panic.
They will find out from the intelligence sent back from the battlefield.
Before that, don't spread this out.
I understand.
Father, what should I do from now on?
From today on, I will have you leave the school.
You must be prepared to be announced as the new Warrior anytime.
Understand?
Yes.
You must be very confused now.
From today on, you must carry on Julius' aspiration as the Warrior,
be the hope of the human race on the front line of the battlefield.
Yes.
You may leave now.
Get some rest.
When this matter is settled, I will see you again.
Brother Julius.
There's no sign of demons in the surrounding 10 km.
Good. Next, let First and Second Squadron guard.
The rest of the soldiers may rest.
Roger.
Not just 10 km, there's no trace of demons in surrounding 30 km.
It seems we won completely.
We didn't win completely.
One tenth of the soldiers died in the battlefield.
Thanks to you, we could end the fight with only these many casualties.
I heard, other fortresses have rather heavy casualties.
Is it because of me?
What humankind can do is limited.
Have you heard about The Nightmare of the Labyrinth?
You mean the mythical monster?
It was 15 years ago...
Buirimus, want to take a rest?
Didn't we just take a rest?
But that was an hour ago.
It was less than an hour ago.
It hurts!
What's going on?
The right leg I injured yesterday is hurting.
But you injured your left leg yesterday.
Hurry up.
You don't have to walk so fast.
Is it because of that?
You want to be back sooner to see your newborn child, right?
That's not it.
Or because you miss your wife?
Mr. Ronandt!
Don't be so angry.
Can you be more alert?
Our duty isn't just exploring.
Many monsters of Great Elroe Labyrinth
have been leaving their habitats recently,
which caused the mainland to be more and more dangerous.
According to the reports of the discovery teams, the taratect is perhaps the reason.
Its danger level is Level A and it's the trickiest S class.
I know, I know.
You mean we should kill it, right?
Things will be fine as long as I'm around. Just follow me.
Mr. Ronandt.
So can we take a rest now?
No.
Petty!
Are you sure this is the place where the spider is seen?
I suppose so.
Seems like it moved its nest elsewhere.
The road leading to Middle Stratum is nearby. Could it have moved there?
Middle Stratum?
But taratects should be afraid of fire. This speculation seems weak.
What's going on?
I don't know either.
I want to move forward, but my body...
What?
Hold on.
Illuminate it with fire and look carefully.
Silk.
We've perhaps found the right place.
SO I'M A SPIDER, SO WHAT?
Abominable!
Can't it be cut off?
Let me burn them.
It may be a little hot. Don't move around.
Okay...
Hold on...
It doesn't catch fire easily.
I want to increase the firepower.
Oh no, the firepower was too strong.
Seriously? Have mercy on me.
I've done too much.
Yes.
If the house owner is around, it will be very mad.
It didn't appear despite the fire. That means it might have given up this place.
Or maybe it was out coincidentally.
Did a monster do this?
Is it really a monster?
This is the way leading to Middle Stratum.
Buirimus.
The house owner is back.
Is it it?
Unbelievable!
What is it?
Mr. Ronandt.
This monster is acting casually while displaying many different skills.
Unbelievable!
It's blocking our way.
Mr. Ronandt, are you okay?
Could that be... the identification skill?
Impossible.
Is the monster identifying me?
THE SICKLE OF DEATH
The Sickle of Death.
Such fatal ability values and so many skills.
What? Ultimate... Wizard?
Mr. Ronandt, come on!
It's frightening. This is too frightening.
What?
IDENTIFICATION IS HINDERED.
It can even hinder my identification skill.
Mr. Ronandt.
It can't be wrong.
It must have caused the abnormality in the labyrinth.
The monsters wanted to escape this force.
Retreat!
Retreat, hurry!
Stop!
I don't know what happened.
This wisdom and strength are beyond my reach.
Let me go!
I want to look at its strength closely.
Mr. Ronandt.
Come on!
If you keep being like this, we will all be dead.
Sorry, it doesn't matter anymore.
Even if we want to retreat, with the road block, we can't.
It will not let us pass as well.
In that case, we can only escape with Mass Teleport.
I understand.
Protect Mr. Ronandt.
Roger.
Mr. Ronandt wants to perform Mass Teleport. We're in charge of buying time.
Kirekock!
Rock Turtle!
Feveroot!
Suiten!
Mr. Ronandt.
Although they're very strong monsters, I don't know if they could come in handy.
Please prepare to teleport quickly.
Again?
Spiders should attack with venom, right?
Abominable! I don't know.
Charge!
Kirekock!
Suiten!
It's not done yet.
Feveroot!
Good. Aim the back of its neck.
What? What happened?
There's no way. Run!
That's the Magic of Wind, like Kirekock's.
How is it possible?
It can cast magic from nothing without using skills.
Rock Turtle!
Rock Turtle, what happened to you?
What?
Just a little more.
How did this happen?
Mr. Ronandt, at least you must live. Go!
Stop the nonsense. You must come back with me.
Mr. Ronandt.
Mr. Buirimus.
We're still in danger.
Call upon the person who knows Healing Magic.
Roger.
Where is the discovery team?
They're all gone.
Mr. Ronandt.
Stay strong.
You have to see your child.
Thank you.
Because of you I could survive.
The so-called strongest wizard of the mankind.
I couldn't do anything at all.
Mr. Ronandt.
In this world,
there are torrents that can't be stopped by human.
Something big is about to happen.
The Nightmare of the Labyrinth
appeared at Kusorion Fortress.
The Queen Taratect who's also one of the taratects.
What does that person want again?
Do you know? This is the prelude.
The life of a spider.
I'm going to start singing.
♫Ordinary♫
♫High school girl♫
♫Ancient literature♫
♫Class♫
♫Suddenly destroyed♫
♫Time♫
♫Process♫
♫Awareness♫
♫Conscious♫
♫Became a spider♫
♫So confusing♫
♫Running here and there in chaos, little spider♫
♫Being helpless in this big labyrinth♫
♫Working hard to survive as the fittest, little spider♫
♫I'll just tell you. My power was weak at the beginning♫
♫Tricky enemies♫
♫Horrible food♫
♫Sweat and tears. What a misfortune♫
♫Don't give up even if your house is burnt down♫
♫But my heart wants my house back♫
♫A dream-like Isekai world of reincarnation♫
♫Needless to be said, the successful people♫
♫are reincarnated as beautiful women♫
♫What? There's no skill that can turn things back?♫
♫Identify. Spin silk. Toss. Shoot♫
♫Focus. Be patient. Eat. Hide. Dodge♫
♫Powerful silk. Venom synthesis. Drugs synthesis♫
♫Gaido attack. Corrosive attack♫
♫Various evil eyes. Final magic. Multiple avatars♫
♫The final skill is to self destroy♫
♫Bring it on♫
♫I can do anything♫
♫Just go on if there's no other way♫
♫Use all kind of skills♫
♫I don't care even if I'm destroyed♫
♫I don't want to die♫
♫I want to live♫
♫I must keep living♫
♫Take this♫
♫I don't want horrible game life♫
♫Life should be better after reincarnation♫
♫Why is my beginning so miserable?♫
♫I will not forgive you, admin D♫
♫The big labyrinth is just as dark today♫
♫Keep living or die trying♫
♫Although this kind of life is quite interesting♫
♫I still can't accept why♫
♫I am a spider♫
I'm so angry!
I'm really angry!
So what? How can this be?
This is annoying!
How dare they break into my house and set fire
while I was out hunting!
And when I was trying to file a complaint, they attacked me.
This is burglary!
Yes!
That was a justifiable defense, right?
I've marked those who escaped.
Marked?
That's one of the abilities of Wisdom.
Wisdom is powerful!
Anyway, it won't be long until I know the exit of the labyrinth.
Experience achieved a certain target.
Level upgraded to level 20.
Hooray!
Various basic ability values have been upgraded.
Upgrade of proficiency skill is rewarded.
Breathless endurance skill upgraded to level four.
Skill points obtained.
Conditions fulfilled.
The Sickle of Death
may evolve to Ede Saine.
Ede Saine?
You're noisy.
Sorry.
Nice rhyme...
The symbol of death.
It's starting to feel like Devil.
Do you want to evolve?
Of course!
Ede Saine, evolution begins.
Forbidden skill is upgraded to level ten.
Oh no.
The forbidden skill is at its highest level...
Loading message.
SO I'M A SPIDER, SO WHAT? NEXT EPISODE: FINAL BATTLE
STAY TUNED!