The strongest primate
high-schooler, Shishio Tsukasa.
You two will never be in danger again.
From now on, I'll do the fighting.
This Shishio guy is way too strong.
Senku, do you intend to bring back
everyone, including the grown-ups
whose hearts are tainted?
This is a stone world.
An untainted paradise.
We'll revive only the pure-hearted youth
and live in a natural
world owned by no one.
It's a chance to purify humanity.
Don't you agree, Senku?
This guy is seriously bad news.
Then again, if we hadn't woken him up,
we would've been killed by the lions.
I guess we didn't really have a choice.
He wants to help out the youth, too,
so I'm sure he'll stay under control until
he learns the recipe for the revival fluid.
Even if it kills me, I have to keep quiet
about the miracle fluid in the cave.
Hey!
Good news, Senku, Tsukasa!
We have a full pot of miracle
fluid from the cave!
For Yuzuriha
We can finally revive Yuzuriha!
What's this "miracle fluid" you speak of?
Let's not waste time standing
here explaining it.
It'll be ten billion times
faster to just show you.
You'd better feel honored to see this.
Time to enjoy the humanity revival show.
Good morning, world
Good Morning World!
How far have I walked?
Only the pain in my feet
Gives me a sense of the distance
The hope for a beautiful view
at the end of a long night
Is what keeps me going today
The mountains of the gods,
the palaces of green
The depths of the caves,
the ends of the deep blue sky
I'll go the full distance,
there are no limits
To the ends of the world
Good morning, world
Good Morning World!
Rid away the impossibility of the dark
An odyssey turning mythology
into the everyday
In this painstaking journey,
turning over every stone
We'll expand our world
Weapons of Science
All right, Yuzuriha.
We're finally going to save you,
for real this time!
What the hell?
This is just short of enough
revival fluid for one person.
What?! Did I take it out too soon?!
Tsukasa and I will play word games
or something while you go get more.
So make a mad dash, big oaf.
Thanks! I'll be right back!
I'll go full speed!
In that case, I'll go, since I'm the fastest.
So would you mind telling me
where this miracle fluid is?
I should've known he'd catch on.
If he learns where the source
of the revival fluid is,
there's a ten billion percent chance
he's going to be able to stop
my Operation: Let's Save Every Last Human.
Did Tsukasa leave?
Yeah, in the blink of an eye.
He's as fast as you'd thi—
Let's make the revival fluid and
bring Yuzuriha back right away,
while Tsukasa isn't here.
Bats...
Touching it makes my finger yellow.
So the "miracle fluid" is nitric acid.
What's going on?
Laboratory
You just said there wasn't
quite enough revival fluid!
Do you really think I'd set out
a pot that was the wrong size?
Good point!
Then why did you send Tsukasa after it?
It was double-edged bait.
I wanted to get rid of him
before reviving Yuzuriha,
even if it meant revealing
where the cave was.
Why do you want to get rid of Tsukasa?
He's a good guy!
That's why he's too much to handle.
I don't have even one millimeter of interest
in his grand vision for a "mighty world."
I find civilization-building
games more exhilarating.
All right.
You don't need to explain.
Senku, I trust what you say.
Something happened while
I was gone, didn't it?
Yeah.
Shishio Tsukasa is a good guy...
and a murderer.
Yuzuriha...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I... I...
I...
I told you we're in a hurry, you big oaf!
You just dumped it all over her!
Couldn't you be a bit more, like... you know!
Wait, nothing's happening!
Is this all right?!
No, it's all right, Yuzuriha!
But is this all right?!
It takes time for the reaction to happen.
This is a kind of cryostasis.
It's like a protective coat made
from trace metals in the body.
Some mysterious mechanism
causes those elements
to phase-shift, maintaining a petrified state.
That's complicated!
Seriously complicated!
It's just a hypothesis, based on a
whole year of painstaking experiments.
The point is, if even one part of it
gets nital on it and breaks down...
it creates a cascade effect that
travels across the entire body.
And the petrification is undone.
Hear me out, Yuzuriha.
For the past five years...
I'm gonna tell Yuzuriha.
I'll survive, even if it kills me!
It's because of you that I was
able to stay alive all this time.
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you.
I've loved you... for hundreds of years...
thousands of years...
Yuzuriha, can you hear me? Yuzuriha!
Taiju-kun?
I'm sorry. I made you wait for 3,700 years...
I'm sorry!
I have no idea what's going on. I just woke up.
But, yeah... I think I know what's going on.
You saved me, didn't you?
Wow... Thanks.
It wasn't me.
It was all thanks to Senku.
Senku spent a whole year
working on the revival fluid.
Sorry to barge in on your reunion chat,
but make up your mind
before Tsukasa gets back.
We only have two options.
Choose one.
Plan A: Taiju and Yuzuriha,
you two run away right now,
and live somewhere far away.
Plan B: we fight together to
stop Tsukasa's murder spree,
using the weapons of civilization.
The answer's obvious!
We're going to fight by your side!
Don't underestimate us, Senku!
Yeah! I have no idea what's
going on, but I'll help, too!
I'm not trying to be nice or anything.
It just seemed logical to give
you both a chance to flee.
If Tsukasa really is killing people, I'll—
Calling it "killing people"
is really a matter of perspective.
I'm culling them... for the
benefit of the new world.
He doesn't even try to hide his
murders from Taiju or Yuzuriha.
In other words, anyone who gets in his way...
Senku, if things go bad,
take care of Yuzuriha for me.
I'm going to stop Tsukasa!
You damn simpleton!
The guy killed a lion with his bare hands.
You're screwed, ten billion percent!
You're forcing me to use the
weapon I've been keeping secret!
I need to shoot it right
between them and stop them!
You're the first person who's managed to
remain standing after receiving my kick.
Yes... And even more interestingly,
it wasn't that you
failed to attack me just now,
but that you refused to.
Why?
I don't hit people!
You can hit me or kick me all you want,
but stop destroying the statues!
Killing people is bad!
Taiju, let me get this straight.
You'll let me keep hitting
you and never fight back,
therefore, don't destroy the statues.
Is that right?
That's right!
I don't understand.
There's no deal being made here.
If you insist on getting in my way...
I don't care how many times you attack me!
I won't stop trying to stop you!
That girl who was just revived...
What if I told you I'd kill her?
I see.
This is why Senku-kun said it might
be more logical for us to flee.
Taiju-kun!
So that did hurt him.
He's bleeding like mad.
We'll have to let him sleep for a few days.
Yes. Let's not fight among ourselves.
You protect Yuzuriha,
instead of worrying about statues
of people you don't know.
And I'll do what I need to do.
I won't let you get in my way.
The crossbow arrow was moving
at over 200 kilometers per hour.
He snatched it right out of the air...
Hey, get up!
Come on! Come on, come on!
You said you'd let him sleep for a few days!
Come on!
You're not gonna go down that easily
in front of Tsukasa, are you, big oaf?
Of course I'm not!
You're okay now?
I'm built to last.
I've got plenty of energy left to spare!
Thank goodness.
Right! Tsukasa!
We need to stop his murdering!
Hold it, big oaf.
I'm not giving up!
How simple-minded can you be?
We just learned that we can't stop him!
Still...
There's only one way to stop
a monster in this stone world.
Advance civilization and
make weapons of science.
Such a waste...
What are you doing, Senku?
I'm making it look like
Tsukasa freaked us out and made
us run off with just our food.
What are you talking about?
Are we running away?
It's just an act.
If we make weapons of science
before he takes notice, we win.
If he finds out first, we lose.
That's the kind of race this is.
We're going to go find
materials to make weapons.
Our goal is Hakone!
Hey, it's just a huge 80-kilometer
adventure, that's all.
Two full marathons, huh?
Five hours ought to do it.
Only for a meathead like you.
The cherry blossoms seem different.
The cherry blossoms we know,
Prunus yedoensis, aren't self-pollinating.
Which means...
They must have gone
extinct right off the bat.
Man, what a great view!
Perfect.
What's that, Senku?
A sextant.
It's been 35,970 seconds
since sunrise as of now.
Did you really just say that
like it's no big deal?
Senku counted for hundreds of billions
of seconds while he was petrified.
This is a piece of cake for him.
A sextant is supposed to tell you
your current location based on the time,
but the accuracy is such trash,
it's a complete joke.
Still, this trash is the only GPS we have.
We must be around Kamakura, I guess.
I wish I knew our exact
longitude and latitude.
Are there any buildings that
could serve as landmarks?
Anything metal is rusted away.
There's nothing left.
What's wrong, Yuzuriha?
Isn't that...
That area's completely bare
of trees for some reason.
Kamakura's landmark is...
I know where we are.
We're at 35 degrees, 19 minutes north,
139 degrees, 32 minutes east.
Look! Look!
What's wrong, Yuzuriha?!
Who made you cry?
Was it me?!
No, I'm not crying!
I mean, it's not that I'm not crying...
But it's not like that, Taiju-kun.
I just woke up today,
and nothing feels real right now.
But seeing the Great Buddha of Kamakura
made me realize we really are in Japan.
It really has been thousands of years...
I started thinking about my mom
and dad, and everyone else...
There's nothing to worry about.
We're about to beat Tsukasa
and save all of humanity.
He's right, Yuzuriha!
And the Great Buddha just told us the way!
He's stood for thousands of years without
falling apart. He really is a god!
Wait, a Buddha?
Well, anyway, something like that!
Well, yeah, they made the
Buddha out of bronze.
Scientifically, it just doesn't rot.
Look!
There's absolutely no
foliage around the Buddha!
It's like he made it so
we could find him easily!
Well, yeah, it's leaking
copper ions like crazy.
It's just poisonous to most plants.
That's it! Bronze!
We can use it to make mirrors!
Time to upgrade my trash sextant!
I'll just help myself to some of this!
Stop!
You blasphemous bastard!
It's a Great Buddha!
Shut up, simpleton! Go away!
No! The Great Buddha!
What the hell are you doing?
I have to protect us from beasts.
Tsukasa might come after us, too.
We're screwed either way if
Tsukasa catches up to us now.
It's illogical to worry about him.
I-I see.
Hurry up and sleep.
Resting is part of your job, too, big oaf.
That giant body's actually
struggling for once, huh?
I'm barely fine!
I'm just tall enough, I mean!
I still have plenty of energy, though!
Not to worry!
Yuzuriha, your toe's still petrified.
Yeah, it does sort of get in the way,
but I guess it's okay.
It's not oka—
That's cold!
Hey, the pain's going away, too.
The revival fluid has
rejuvenating properties, too?
No, it doesn't.
It's just that the small cracks get mended
when the petrification is reversed.
Haven't you noticed we're still alive
even though our faces are cracked?
That's true.
Let's head to our goal.
If you want to take a bath
in actual rejuvenating fluid.
When you say the goal in
Hakone, do you mean...
A room in disarray, hurried footsteps...
Did they run away in a panic?
Yes... That's what they're
trying to make me think.
How can I tell?
Senku, you aren't the kind
of man to turn tail and run.
Why did he lie about Taiju being unable to move, and then secretly head west?
It's obvious.
Senku is trying to make weapons
of science to fight against me.
But where?
We made it to the goal!
Hot springs!
Wow...
There's a great view of Mount Fuji, too.
You two better not have forgotten
why we came all this way.
So what's this "weapon of science"?
The greatest invention in human history...
Smartphones?!
You sure love your smartphone.
No.
Guns.
We're making gunpowder.
The stone age was two million years ago.
And gunpowder was invented
just recently, around 700 AD.
Basically, we're about to warp
1,998,700 years ahead in civilization.
This is exhilarating.
Hakone.
If they make gunpowder,
I don't stand a chance.
I'm going to stop them
before Senku can make it.
Thankfully, Japan is full of volcanoes.
Go to any hot spring, and you have
an all-you-can-carry bargain sale
of sulfur, the main component of gunpowder.
It's the birth of our ultimate
anti-Tsukasa weapon: black powder.
Maybe I don't know what to do
Hurry up, my mind is on the moon
Flying up to where the wind blew
In my hands awakens
The passion overflowing
Just wandering through this world
Your one shining pure
Could never be pierced
with a rusty knife
I'm burning like a fire gone wild
The moment an arrow
shot through my heart
The noise plaguing me was released
Everything was different
from that moment on
If I don't try, I'll never know
Why do flowers bloom?
Your voice echoes
Tell me why?
I just shouted to the sky
But you are no no no longer here,
that's right?
The life we confirmed that day
You can call it a fleeting
dream if you want
But I'll save you from a wounded today
Fire the Smoke Signal
Next Episode
This is a work of fiction, but the plants,
animals, and production methods described are based on reality.
Foraging and making things on your own accord is extremely dangerous
and, in some cases, illegal. Please do not imitate without expertise.