Lord Veldora, it's a check.
Hmm, you've improved well, Ifrit.
Thank you.
That's the spirit, Ifrit.
Climb your way up to my level.
I shall wait eagerly for that day to come.
Y-Yes!
But I'm the one who won this time, though.
However, we might not have that much time left.
Lord Veldora?
I might not be able to stay here for much longer.
Wh-What did you say?!
The time I spent with you was wonderful.
A lot has happened.
Let's give a name to a nameless flower
So that it won't freeze from the coldness of solitude
If it's as frail as it is beautiful
Then it's not as fragile anymore
Like how you paint color on a transparent body
Beyond the page of the chapter
It's welcoming you with a smile
Whenever, as much as it takes
Let's start a new world
We're Storyteller
All the love, hope, envy
Even the song of despair we sing today
It will all be a seed and bloom, into a strong person
Why does salvation born from someone's tear
That's just sad
Ideal and fantasy, all mixed up by youthful impulse
My real self, is now reborn!
After Rimuru fulfilled his mission to save Shizu's students in Engrassia,
he returns to Tempest.
That mask...
What about it?
It appears to be the one worn by the Hero who sealed me.
Or maybe it just looks like one?
So the hero handed it to Shizu, and it goes to Chloe through Rimuru.
Is there some sort of connection?
Nah, it can't be. Yeah, I'm just overthinking it.
That time I thought the peaceful days will just continue
after Rimuru's back at monster town.
I also didn't think much about it.
But one of Shizu's disciple, Sakaguchi Hinata.
Because of Hinata's wide range barrier,
the magicule in the area gets purified
and Lord Rimuru is unable to use his full power.
That woman really just won't listen to anything he says.
She seems to be quite hard-headed.
I never thought someone would corner Lord Rimuru like this.
He might lose.
N-No way!
Is it okay?
If he dies, then we won't be safe either.
Fret not.
Just believe in Rimuru and watch.
Rimuru has an idea.
Exhaust everything!
Disintegration!
As I expect of him.
Rimuru already prepared a Body Double in advance.
He lets his Body Double fight Hinata, while the real him hides in safety.
H-How clever of him!
It's still a risky bet, but I'm impressed.
Looks like he can go home now.
About that, I actually sensed something odd.
Nnn?
Something is happening in Tempest?
The human is blinded by greed and attacks the nation of monsters.
They really are a bothersome creature.
But Rimuru wishes to coexist with those humans.
Yes, perhaps he is trying to follow the rules of human.
He appears to be really calm.
But inside, his emotion is anything but stable.
I can feel his rage trying to gush out.
Let's just hope nothing will hurt Rimuru's heart any further.
There is no words to describe it.
Yes.
I've only known Shion through Rimuru, but I do feel a bit attached to her.
I respect her, as there are stuff to be learned from her.
But now she...
It is hard for me to see Rimuru being sad like this.
But a monster's death is nothing to be mourned for.
Their soul will simply return to the cycle of life and death,
allowing them to eventually reach an even higher height.
That's what the law of nature is all about.
Yes, that is correct.
Then why don't he just accept it and move on?
Why would he feel this sad?
Don't you feel lonely, Lord Veldora?
You can no longer meet Ms. Shion, and her bright, pure, respectable personality.
I suppose the stronger their bond is, the sadder he feels for her lost.
It is just recently that I realized that.
I see.
I might be averting my eyes from Shion
by accepting her death as part of the law of nature.
I once killed this girl named Pirina who was friends with Shizu.
At the time, my ego still haven't been fully developed,
and I was merely reacting to any hostility I detect.
Even so, that is still the sin that I committed.
And that was the main factor
on why Shizu and I was unable to be fully connected.
Ifrit...
It's already too late.
I also accepted death merely as part of the law of nature,
so I wasn't able to notice Shizu's pain.
Shizu thought what I did was her fault,
and tormented her heart as a result.
If I hadn't observed Lord Rimuru alongside you,
I wouldn't be able to understand that no matter how long it takes.
Death is not something to be taken lightly.
A-Actually!
The chance might be slim.
No, there might not even be a chance.
But there is a fairytale about resurrecting someone from the dead!
-Lord Veldora! -Resurrect the dead?!
If such a thing does exist...
A story about a certain girl and a dragon.
Her parents were a dragon and a human, and she was raised as the Dragon Princess.
One day, her dragon father made a small copy of himself
and gave it to his daughter to be her friend.
This story... and this Dragon Princess...
Yes, it's about Milim.
I don't really know much, but...
If this barrier is also keeping the souls of the dead inside...
The probability for that is 3.14%.
The success rate for resurrection is 3.14%.
That's good enough.
Look, seems like Rimuru also thinks the same way.
He's all fired up.
Yes, he's all prepared.
Yeah.
He's prepared to take over 100,000 human life,
shoulder the weight of that sin, and become a True Demon Lord.
Rimuru.
Rest assured.
You're not alone.
I will shoulder that sin alongside you.
So they're the ones who killed Shion and others...
Well then.
Let's start.
Their counterattack finally begins.
Yes, and the air is trembling as if it's responding to Rimuru's anger.
The anger of Rimuru's friends is also tremendous.
Even those who are usually calm
looks like a completely different person now.
But still, I can't believe Rimuru said;
"If I ended up becoming a mindless monster,
take command of everyone left who can fight and dispose me immediately."
to Beminaru before the fight.
What a cruel thing to ask, don't you think?
If I were him, I wouldn't accept that.
True. It might be possible in the past, but not the case now.
I don't have what it takes to command other monsters to begin with.
And stopping Lord Rimuru would be impossible.
That's part of the reason.
I'm sure Rimuru is not the type to make an unreasonable request,
so that just means how much he believes and relies on Benimaru.
I do feel a little bit jealous.
Well, I'm sure Rimuru won't do anything that would make his friend sad.
He will surely succeed in becoming a Demon Lord.
You're right. Let's believe in him.
Ah, Lord Veldora. Look.
Die.
May the wrath of the gods sear through your very souls.
Megiddo!
That gentle Rimuru...
Although he had always hated to hurt other people,
he's killing enemy forces without showing any hesitation.
He chooses the most optimal method to kill
and put it into action without hesitation.
To be honest, one can't help but to feel dread seeing his resolve.
Yes.
The calm one is always the scariest when angry.
There's a lot of depiction of that in the scriptures.
He's also surprisingly calm for not killing Edmaris the king of Falmuth.
If I were him, I would never bother to do such a thing.
I will just kill them all.
However, if you think about it,
that will make it harder to clean after the mess.
Even Falmuth won't stay put if their king is killed,
and I'm sure they will move their entire army response.
And the Western Holy Church won't simply stay put either.
Considering the goal is to avoid any further conflict,
then what Lord Rimuru did might be for the best.
It's a hard issue.
However, the fact that he wouldn't kill the king
doesn't mean he will show any mercy.
If it were me, I would just kill him right there.
Rimuru really did great holding back.
What an incredible mental strength.
However, I suppose it really is the best option.
Nn? He's finally evolving.
Rimuru is acting weird.
He looks like dozing off.
I've never experienced it, so I don't know first hand.
But I'm sure evolving into a Demon Lord is a tiring ordeal.
Nnn?! That guy... he must be an Archdemon.
-Eh?! -I'm sure of it.
Not to mention, it's not just some ordinary guy who was just born.
But a very dangerous one who has lived for so many years.
No way?!
Ifrit, as a high-level spirit who have advantages against demons,
can you tell how much is his strength?
Yes, but he looks like just ordinary Greater Demon in my eyes.
That means he has fully mastered Mimic to conceal his identity.
On top of that, he's an oddball who comes even though no one calls him.
There's a chance that he might have lived longer than me.
No, it can't be.
I'm bored.
Bored?
Lord Veldora, we're at the most intense situation right now.
Don't you have any other thing to say?
But I'm just telling the truth.
Now that Rimuru has fallen asleep for his evolution,
we can't even see what's happening outside.
There just nothing to do, it's boring.
But well, just playing around won't do any good.
I'm sure it'll be busy once Rimuru becomes a Demon Lord.
I must hurry up and get myself out of this Unlimited Imprisonment to help him.
I'll go back analyzing the Unlimited Imprisonment now.
Good luck!
-Nnn? -What's wrong?
-This is weird. -Lord Veldora?
My analyzing speed increased tremendously.
Or more like, I feel stronger.
More than double, it's dozen... hundred times faster!
No, my analyzing speed has now become hundreds of times faster!
I'm so amazing!
As I expect from you, Lord Veldora!
Unlimited Imprisonment is a piece of cake when you put your mind to it!
Wait wait wait!
Not even I would be that conceited.
That is just impossible.
There's no way I would become stronger without any reason.
By the way, how much stronger do you feel right now?
It's still increasing, but around 345 times stronger, I guess?
What?!
Well, I knew you would say that.
I mean, it's weird!
No matter how you think about it, it's strange!
Ermm... did you eat anything weird lately?
You ate something from the ground, didn't you?
Cut that out!
I'm sorry, I was shocked.
By the way, Lord Veldora, why are you so calm about this?
Well, because it's better this way.
If things continue like this,
I will get out of this place in no time!
Well, that's true.
So do you have any idea on why that is happening?
I do have one.
It seems that Rimuru's analyzing speed also increased.
Here's my guess.
In the process of transforming into a Demon Lord,
the computing ability of Rimuru's skill has improved.
And at the same time, it also improves your skill?
-Then that's great. -Nnn?
-Well, your life. -My life?!
I was a little worried,
thinking that the boost was simply the last glimmer of your life.
That is impossible! Hahaha!
No way, right?
Don't scare me like that.
Lord Veldora! Look at that!
Seems like Rimuru's evolution into a Demon Lord is finally over.
What's that?
Must be "Gift."
When you evolve into a Demon Lord,
a Gift will be distributed to all monsters within your genealogy.
I see.
L-Lord Veldora!
Why? How did this happen?
Lord Veldora, this person whom we thought were Lord Rimuru... could it be...?
-I noticed from the start, though. -Eh?
I already realized that Rimuru's skill was special from the start.
Yes, that it is an independent type.
As I expect from you, Lord Veldora... or so you think I will say?!
Up until now, you've always been smug when you explain stuff to me.
Ifrit, Shion and orders are waking up!
However...
L-Lord Raphael?!
My instinct is telling me that I must not oppose this thing.
May I ask what business do you need from us today?
No matter what it is, I, Ifrit, shall obey your every command!
Yes. The species Ifrit has no name and a weak ego.
Therefore, you do not possess sufficient foundation to obtain a skill.
I recommend you to resume your training.
Roger!
I, Ifrit, shall now begin my training!
One, two, three, four, five!
Ummm...
Report.
I am convinced that the individual Veldora has been slacking off too much.
Order.
Acquire Ultimate skill immediately.
But that's kind of impossible...
Report. It's possible.
I've expanded this computing space by force.
You shall maintain this space by yourself
while continuing your work analyzing the Unlimited Imprisonment.
She didn't ask whether I can do it or not, so that means it's an order.
We must do it, I guess.
Yes!
I did my best and finally acquire one!
My Ultimate skill, Faust!
It's thanks to this Gift from Rimuru, I must thank him later.
Now Lord Raphael won't be yelling at us.
Yeah.
And also, Ifrit, you got a lot more muscular, aren't you?
No, I still have more to go.
I will train harder and lower my body fat percentage to 10%!
I see. Well, do your best.
Question.
Have you acquired an Ultimate Skill?
Yes of course!
Good.
Well then, let's break this Unlimited Imprisonment right away.
Now you can finally get out! Congratulation, Lord Veldora!
It's still too early to celebrate, though. Hahaha!
What should I talk about with Rimuru after I break free?
I'll start with a boast!
For that, I will pretend that I don't know anything that happened outside.
That sounds good.
Maybe I can pretend to acquire Faust in front of him.
"O-Oooh! So this is what my evolved skill is like?!"
"My Unique Skill Inquirer have became Ultimate Skill Faust!"
"It is a power that embodies my restless pursuit of knowledge!"
That's what I'll say.
"That's amazing, Veldora!"
"You just got an Ultimate Skill so easily!"
"As I thought, you're an incredible dude!"
Like that, Rimuru will surely complement me from the bottom of his heart.
After that, I will say this to him.
"It's no big deal."
Ummm, Lord Veldora, if I may...
If you're going to go outside and stand as Lord Rimuru's friend,
Lord Rimuru will have to take responsibility for your action.
Please remember that.
People have this thing called "Unwelcome favor."
It means things that you do out of goodwill can still be an annoyance for others.
And for someone as powerful as you,
I believe it's better if you first consult with others before you start.
I see.
Understand? You don't want Lord Rimuru to hate you, don't you?
I'll cry.
As such, you need to be cautious,
careful, thoughtful, and think about others.
It's a promise.
Yes, I understand.
And Ifrit, I will promise you this.
Promise?
I promise that someday I will free you from that place.
R-Really?! I will eagerly wait for that day to come!
Rest assured, Ifrit.
Like Rimuru, I'm the type who always keeps his promise.
And I'm sure it won't take long until I fulfill our promise.
I'll be looking forward to be with you again.
Yes, of course!
When that time comes, please have another shogi match with me.
I won't hold back.
Just as I want it!
This place sure takes me back.
It has been two years since then.
Report.
Analysis and Assessment of Unlimited Imprisonment is complete.
I can finally fulfill my promise.
I will free you now.
Veldora!
I grew taller?!
Raphael, make a Body Double of me.
I'll make it as the vessel for Veldora.
Enhanced Replication activate.
My body did grew a bit.
It's supposed to be me, but man, I look beautiful.
Okay, let's do this.
Please work.
Report.
The soul corridor between Master and the individual Veldora has been established.
I, the Storm Dragon Veldora Tempest, have returned!
Anyone who opposes me will die!
I'm used to losing things
I said it like it's someone else's problem
It's a blurry realism
Because it's not about me
The nameless sadness disappears, warped in a legato-like dream
Will we feel better if we hug each other?
The life which I repeat is a joined miracle
Don't forget me, pass your voice to me
If I were to live for someone's sake
I wish that someone is you (I'll tell you one more story)
If I can redo this world once again
I will paint that story with love
You'll know how this story's gonna end
I will tell you
I will tell you one more story
You'll know how this story's gonna end
I will tell you