-It's just around that corner!
-Okay!
It's Moebius.
Draken-kun!
Hey, Mitsuya.
Takemicchi.
Takemicchi! Mitsuya!
Emma-chan!
Peh-yan, you bastard!
Why are you teaming up with Moebius?!
Shut up, Mitsuya! We will kill you too!
You guys really think you can win
with just the two of you?
Mikey...
Mikey-kun!
Who made you do this?
It doesn't matter who I am.
But I'm in charge of Moebius.
For this moment, at least.
I'm Hanma.
Moebius's entire gang, 100 people!
Versus four guys from Toman!
Good grief.
You guys...
The entire Tokyo Manji
Gang's now here, jackass!
This is getting fun.
Let's go!
Kill 'em all!
This is bad! It started!
I must protect Draken-kun no matter what!
Draken-kun!
I... don't want to fight you.
Come back to us, Peh-yan.
There he is.
I found him! It's Kiyomasa-kun!
I did it! I finally did it!
Draken...
Draken!
Draken-kun!
No way! It can't be true!
What happened, Takemicchi?!
Draken-kun...
...he got stabbed!
Move out!
Get out of my way!
Hanma!
Mikey.
Found cha'!
How dull~
We got our collars grabbed
and took an intense punch
After we got beaten up
Together we crouched
The anticipated rain came
"This should clean your bruise"
you lied with a smile
Even though you're bad at argument
So stop making such lame jokes
It's so bad I teared up
Getting blue bruises all the time
I cry, cry, and cry
Leaning our unstable heart together
We fight against the rotten Bad End
I wonder why
The pleasant pain was more vivid,
even more than the happiness
Clicking our tongue over our wet clothes
We look at each other's face and laugh
The Revenge we swore in that rainy night
It's over!
Everything is over!
Draken... died!
Takemicchi!
He's still alive!
Mikey-kun!
Take care of Ken-chin!
Eh?
Me?
That's right.
I...
...must do something!
He's heavy.
I feel like my body is giving up already.
Draken-kun!
It'll be fine.
I will carry you to the hospital.
I promise you...
Everything is gonna be alright!
Keep it together, my body!
Takemichi-kun!
Hina! Emma-chan!
I will call the ambulance now.
How's Draken?
Don't worry. He's still alive.
It's taking too much time.
Hina, we're supposed to wait
for the ambulance here, right?
Yeah, but...
It seems like the road's packed
because of the festival and the rain.
Seriously?
Takemichi-kun?
Why... are they here?
Oooh? The little sweet
Draken ain't dead yet!
Hey! Why Wimpy-michi is here?
How dare a little shit like you
giving me trouble here?
Hey, someone go get
some duct tape again.
It's over.
Takemicchi.
Draken-kun...
You shouldn't move.
Thank you.
Takemicchi.
Take Hina-chan and Emma
with you and run.
I... am fine.
Run?
Did I... try to run just now?
And he noticed that?
Hurry up, Takemicchi.
Even though he was beaten up this bad?
And I...
...already lost everything
because I kept running away.
Am I going to run away for the second time?
Takemichi-kun?
I'm so pathetic.
Just why did I come here
in the first place?
Hina, stay back.
Draken-kun.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for giving me courage.
Takemicchi?
If I run now, everything will be over.
It's not just for other people's sake.
What do you want?
Do you want to die, shithead?
You sure you don't wanna
run away, Moron-michi?!
I won't run away.
This time, I won't run anymore.
For everything
that happened in my life...
...This is my revenge!
Kiyomasa-kun.
We haven't settled it, have we?
Huh?
That one-on-one back
at the underground fight.
Huh?
What the heck are you talking about?
No matter how you look at it,
it's your darn lost!
I didn't lose.
Ooh.
Then I bet 100 million yen on Takemicchi.
-Eh?
-Huh?
It's bullshit, but I'll play along.
I bet 100 million yen on Takemichi, too!
I bet 300 million yen!
Hina? Emma-chan?!
These guys just lost their
damn minds, didn't they?
We didn't.
Huh?
Takemicchi will win.
Thank you, everyone.
Let's go, Kiyomasa!
Let's fight!
Really? I thought that'd do the trick.
You surprisngly got a nice reflex, huh?
Takemichi-kun!
Hina, it's dangerous! Stay back!
Let go! Takemichi-kun is in danger!
I have no interest in doing one-on-one.
This is an execution!
Kiyomasa you rad!
I will kill you, Hanagaki.
We'll dominate the whole country!
Huh?
What is it, all of the sudden?
If you wanna live as a delinquent,
then the question is
how far you can climb up
with just your fist!
I thought I could become
the number one delinquent in Tokyo.
The first step is Shibuya Third Mid.
But that dream was quickly crushed.
I couldn't become Mikey-kun.
What's wrong, Hanagaki?
You haven't landed a single
punch on me yet.
"My awful life was all this guy's fault."
I'll beat you to death.
"I was unlucky."
That's what I thought.
But I was wrong.
All of that...
It's all my fault!
I didn't fight back
just because I lost once.
It's all because of my weakness!
Takemichi-kun!
Hanagaki, your girl gonna
get disillusioned hard.
She'll learn you're as weak as flies.
Is clinging to him all you can do?
That's just lame!
That hurt!
He bit him!
That's just pathetic, wimp-michi!
What are you, an elementary schooler?
Let go of me, you bastard!
It doesn't matter if I'm lame.
It doesn't matter if I'm pathetic.
It doesn't matter if I can't
become Mikey-kun!
I am...
TAKEMICHI HANAGAKI!!!
You are you.
This is my second life.
I won't give up on it this time!
Let me go!
Don't let go of him, Takemicchi!
You shit!
I won.
My revenge...
...Succeeds!
-Takemichi-kun!
-Don't come, Hina!
I showed my guts, Naoto.
I... beat Kiyomasa.
But, sorry... Naoto.
The mission failed.
Don't mind it.
Kiyomasa's so lame.
Now you got a nice story
to tell in the afterlife.
Hina.
Run with Emma-chan.
Takemichi-kun...
We'll handle this ourselves somehow.
But...
It'll be okay.
We will surely be okay.
I beg you.
Draken-kun.
What do you think heaven is like?
You'll go straight down to hell.
But I didn't do anything bad.
Oh, look, they're getting all fired up.
They pissed me off.
I can't feel my left hand anymore.
And I can't even lift my right hand.
You look like someone could topple
you with just one finger, Takemicchi.
Same goes for you.
End them!
In the end, I couldn't change the future.
But I did my best.
I won't look down until the very end!
Why are you sobbing like that?
Crybaby hero!
Akkun!
Everyone!
Mizo Mid Five has arrived!
Tachibana called us.
Leave this to us!
We can kick some ass
when we put our minds to it!
Float like a crane!
Sting like a horsefly!
You dumbass!
You guys are just
some pussies in a group.
What can you even do?
Draken-kun.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't protect you just by myself.
Since my first time coming to this place,
I haven't been able to do anything right.
But!
Your effort here is useless.
Useless?
Even if it's really useless...
Fight me one-on-one.
Even so!
I ain't giving up!
There is time where
giving up is not an option!
Isn't that right, Takemichi?
I definitely won't lose!
Everyone...
Thank you.
It's our...
...victory!
I just want to be right next to you
Next to your slightly sweaty shirt
The rain falls all of the sudden
So I kissed you on that lonely night
If you look back, I will always
be there and smiling at you
Please
Give up on that unachievable future
Take it now
In the real new world
If I have to give you a name,
it's "My Hero"
That straight wish
Will go beyond the stopped time
"I don't need anyone but you"
I will keep living here
Break down that crooked needle
Shout out that firm words
Kick away that unmeaning destiny