It's our victory!
Crap! It's the cop!
What should we do, Red?!
Let's get out of here!
Okay!
What about Kiyomasa-kun?
Leave him!
I've been running around,
doing stuff I'm not good at.
But none of them are pointless.
Because they're always
watching after me.
Thank you.
We did it, Takemichi.
Did you see my super miracle punch?
I did see you getting punched.
Everyone, don't just stand there!
Hurry up and take Draken-kun
and Takemichi to the ambulance!
-Ouch.
-Takemichi, stop your bleeding with this.
Draken-kun, can you stand?
-Somehow.
-Just where's the ambulance?!
Over here! Hurry!
Everyone! Here!
Hurry up!
-Come on! Come on!
-Hey, over here!
Man, I'm beat.
Heey!
We're done over here.
This guy just busted up his foot.
Got it, where's Mikey?
Over there.
Dull, isn't it, Mikey?
You don't even lose your breath,
what a monster.
Shut up.
Just die already.
Hanma-san, 'bout time.
Yeah.
Crap! It's the cop!
Get out of here!
Mikey.
The strongest and worst Bosozoku
alliance in Kanto will be born soon.
It's Valhalla!
I am Valhalla's first Vice-President.
Shuji Hanma.
Remember that, Mikey.
From now on, there will
be no peace for Toman.
We got our collars grabbed
and took an intense punch
After we got beaten up
Together we crouched
The anticipated rain came
"This should clean your bruise"
you lied with a smile
Even though you're bad at argument
So stop making such lame jokes
It's so bad I teared up
Getting blue bruises all the time
I cry, cry, and cry
Leaning our unstable heart together
We fight against the rotten Bad End
I wonder why
The pleasant pain was more vivid,
even more than the happiness
Clicking our tongue over our wet clothes
We look at each other's face and laugh
The Revenge we swore in that rainy night
Please be okay!
Draken-kun!
Thank you.
Takemicchi.
You're my savior.
Please, don't say that.
It isn't like you at all, Draken-kun.
Take care of... Mikey for me.
Eh?
He's going into cardiac arrest!
Sit back!
His JCS has dropped! Initiating CPR!
One! Two! Three!
Four! Five! Six!
-He's not coming back!
-One more time!
No way!
Draken-kun!
(Now Operating)
Takemichi-kun.
Hina...
Emma-chan... Everyone...
-No way...
-Cardiac arrest?
This can't be true.
Tell me it's not.
I'm scared. Hina....
Emma-chan...
Takemicchi!
How's Draken?!
Mitsuya-kun! Peh-yan-kun!
Before we got to the hospital,
his pulse was already...
SHIT!
Mikey-kun...
Draken-kun is--
-Mikey.
-Mikey, I..!
You're being too loud.
We're in the hospital,
so keep it down.
Where's the waiting room?
Mikey...
Ken-chin.
He's the type of guy
who always keeps his words.
He won't drop at a place like this.
I definitely won't let it end like this.
He...
He promised me that
we'd take the top together.
So Emma, Mitsuya, Peh-yan...
Takemicchi.
Believe in Ken-chin.
Everything will be fine.
He's right.
Losing our cool isn't gonna help.
Mikey-kun really is strong.
Listen, don't make commotion.
(Now Operating)
We stopped his life from passing.
Eh?
The surgery...
...was a success.
HELL YEEEEEAAAAH!!!
Draken-kun is saved!
-Hina!
-Thank goodness! I'm so happy for you!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Keep it down, guys.
Let's go tell the guys waiting outside.
Yes!
Peh-yan-kun?
I...
I can't meet up with everyone.
Peh-yan.
Everyone will understand that
you did all that for Pah-chin.
Mitsuya...
But Peh-yan, the one who thinks about
Pah-chin the most is Draken.
Still going though you can't meet him?
Ah?
It's fine, no big deal.
Ever since that incident, he goes with
Pah-chin's parents and visits him every day.
He would always bring gifts even
though only relatives can meet him,
and he'd wait outside by himself
during the whole visit.
And that's the guy
you tried to kill!
Draken...!
You'd better apologize.
To Draken, to Pah-chin.
And to everyone.
Welcome back, Peh-yan.
Ooh, the rain stopped.
Ah! What should I do?
Look at the time!
It's past midnight!
It's August 4th already.
Eh?
You must save Ken Ryuguji on August 3rd.
That's your mission this time.
It's already August 4th.
Naoto.
I made it.
August 3rd is over.
I protected Draken!
Mission complete!
All of you be quiet!
There's no way Draken
would die like that!
-Yeah!
-But man, I'm so glad.
Okay, let's go home now.
Eh?
Where's Mikey-kun?
That's weird, where did he go to?
Ah, Mike-!
Thank goodness!
Ken-chin!
Don't make me worry like that.
August 10th.
One week after the big
brawl of August 3rd.
Rumor about the fight spreads...
Ah! It's Takemichi-senpai!
Eh? You mean that guy
who stopped the battle of 8/3?
Seriously?! He's so cool!
I've become "The Man of Hour" overnight
among the city's delinquents.
Crap! I can't return to the future now!
Why did we waste our
time saving this jackass?
Draken-kun!
I'm here to visit ya'!
How the things goin'?
Quit acting like a jackass.
E-Eh? How am I acting like one?
It's written all over your body.
Don't get carried away just because
you get a little attention, dumbass!
That's lame.
You would never understand, Draken-kun.
Just how I feel living under the shadow.
Huh? Creep.
I've never been looked up
by anyone before!
Just let me enjoy it a little, okay?!
I'm impressed you'd admit something
that depressing so loudly.
Tch, you're no fun.
You said I was your savior, but when
you start getting better it's back to this.
That's right.
Here.
Mikey told me to give this to you.
A Tokko-fuku!
It's the uniform Mikey wore
when he first started Toman.
For Toman, it's as important as life itself.
Why is he giving me something
this valuable?
It's up to you whether to
wear it or not.
But he said he wants you to keep it.
Takemicchi, you're a benefactor for Toman.
Everyone acknowledges that.
I'm one of them.
Let me give you my thanks once again.
Thank you.
That uniform.
Take good care of it.
Mikey-kun's...
This is too heavy for me.
Do you think I can be a man
worthy of this one day?
Go see him.
Eh?
I'm sure he's taking a nap on the rooftop.
Mikey-kun.
This doesn't feel right.
Eh?
I can't shake off this
weird feeling in my head.
Why did Hanma try to start
an infight within Toman?
Why did he try to kill Ken-chin
using Kiyomasa and his group?
But the biggest mystery...
You knew about the infight and
that Ken-chin would be targeted
before anyone else.
And you tried to stop both from happening.
Takemicchi.
Just what are you?
I...
What's with that lame outfit?
Eh?
You always look lame, though.
E-Erm, well, this is just...
Well, whatever.
Eh?
Ken-chin is saved thanks to you.
Thank you, Takemicchi.
Mikey-kun, Draken-kun, Akkun.
To be honest, I want to
stay with them forever.
But I must go home now.
Everyone... goodbye.
Takemichi-kun?
You always come to my house
without notice.
Sorry 'bout that.
Anyway, is Naoto here?
Naoto! Takemichi-kun is calling you!
Just wait here.
Ah, Hina!
Here.
Eh? A necklace?
You know, for failing to make it up to
you and getting you caught up in that.
Ah, you mean the festival?
So I'm like making up
for not making up.
It's cheap though.
Four-leaf clover?
Yeah.
Can I put it on?
Sure.
Actually, it's not just for that.
I want to leave something
tangible behind.
What do you think?
Because I won't be able to
meet the current you anymore.
Yeah, it looks good on you.
Thank you.
I'll cherish it.
Errm...
I'm sorry for interrupting while
you two are flirting...
But did you need something from me?
Since when you're there?!
Nice gift.
Hey, you were eavesdropping?!
I just came because you called.
Then why didn't you say something?!
Naoto.
Handshake.
Eh?
You like handshaking, Takemichi-kun?
Well yeah.
Hina.
Have a merry life.
What's up with that?
Naoto.
Okay.
I prevented Draken's death.
Now Draken will remain as the second
top member of Toman in the present.
And Kisaki won't be.
Mikey who changed because
of Draken-kun's death.
Akkun who committed suicide
because of his fear of Kisaki.
And lastly, Hina who was killed by
the evil Toman in the present.
If Draken's still alive,
everything should change!
Isn't that right, Naoto?
How many times are you going to make me
say the same thing, Takemichi Hanagaki-kun?
Eh?
Manager?
When a DVD gets returned,
put it back on display immediately.
Please do it now.
I'm at work?!
Eh? Eh?
Wait a second, what's going on?
Didn't I get fired
from my part-time job?
Huh? Eh?
What about Naoto?
Ah! My phone!
No matter how many times I searched,
I can't find the news of Hina's death!
Was my time leap all just a dream?
A-Anyway, I must call Naoto.
Why is Naoto's number not in here?!
It wasn't a dream.
My schedule notification?
Hairdresser? What's this?
Akkun!
What is he doing?
That was fast,
what about your part-time job?
I left early.
Don't get fired, okay?
Akkun.
Did you become a hairdresser?
Huh? I'm still in training.
I told you I am still an assistant.
I called you today because...
I'll finally be allowed to
cut people's hair next month.
I want you to be my haircut model.
You know, as my first customer.
You promised, didn't you?
I will be your first customer.
O-Okay...
Great! It's a promise, okay!
What is it? You didn't forget, did you?
Dumbass! No way I'd forget!
Are you crying?
Dumbass! I'm not crying!
You're a crybaby as always, Takemichi.
I finally understand.
I changed the present!
I really succeed!
I don't know this number.
Hello?
So you succeed.
Huh? Who?
And you returned
from the past just now.
Naoto!
Amazing. You really did it.
Everything has changed.
Takemichi-kun.
Let's go meet my sister.
Eh?!
Hina is alive!
I just want to be right next to you
Next to your slightly sweaty shirt
The rain falls all of the sudden
So I kissed you on that lonely night
If you look back, I will always
be there and smiling at you
Please
Give up on that unachievable future
Take it now
In the real new world
If I have to give you a name,
it's "My Hero"
That straight wish
Will go beyond the stopped time
"I don't need anyone but you"
I will keep living here
Break down that crooked needle
Shout out that firm words
Kick away that unmeaning destiny