Let's take a little walk, Takemichi-kun.
Okay.
This park takes me back.
I came here with someone I liked.
I-I see...
On Christmas Eve.
Even now, I still can't forget that person.
Eh?
Why was I dumped?
I still don't get it.
Sorry! I-I need to go to the toilet!
I must change.
I will ask her out!
Eh?
You're not in the car?
Hina!
HINA!!!
Take... michi...?
Why... are you... not in the... car?
Akkun?!
Hina! Let's get out of here!
My legs...
I can't... feel it anymore...
I will definitely save you!
No matter how many times I fail!
I will try over and over!
Until I reach the future where
you're saved...
I definitely won't give up!
Hina...
You always come without notice.
Hina!
I love you!
Umm, are you okay?
We understand your feeling.
But other people need their
turn as well, so please.
Umm...
Is there anything wrong?
Please, take a rest.
Umm, can you hear us?
Just why...?!
I thought everything went well!
Naoto...
Sis...
Takemichi Hanagaki-kun?
I'm Hinata's mother.
Long time no see.
How's Naoto?
He's fine.
He has calmed down a bit.
I see...
Thank goodness.
Here.
For me?
Open it.
This is...
It seemed to be her favorite.
She always wore it like
it's the most precious thing.
It was a gift from you, wasn't it?
She must've loved you very much.
Hina...
We got our collars grabbed
and took an intense punch
After we got beaten up
Together we crouched
The anticipated rain came
"This should clean your bruise"
you lied with a smile
Even though you're bad at argument
So stop making such lame jokes
It's so bad I teared up
Getting blue bruises all the time
I cry, cry, and cry
Leaning our unstable heart together
We fight against the rotten Bad End
I wonder why
The pleasant pain was more vivid,
even more than the happiness
Clicking our tongue over our wet clothes
We look at each other's faces and laugh
The Revenge we swore in that rainy night
I did some research on Atsushi Sendo.
This time he was married
and had children.
Eh? He was?
If he had a family,
then why did he do this?
Right now, his family is missing.
Eh?
His family was likely kidnapped
and used to coerce him.
Did Sendo say anything
before just before he died?
Yeah.
The same thing as before.
That Toman is controlled by Kisaki.
Toman again?
Come to think of it,
what was Hanma doing there?
So in the end...
We couldn't change anything.
Whatever we do, it's useless.
Fate can't be changed.
You're wrong, Naoto.
Even though we did save Draken-kun,
nothing has changed.
That means it's not the reason
why Toman turned evil in the first place.
When Hina died in front of me.
As I watched the flames raise,
I understood something.
We have to fix things down to its root.
Its root?
I will crush Toman!
To do that, I will become
the top member of Toman in the past!
I thought you have some good ideas...
I'm serious!
But that's reckless.
Doesn't matter!
I'll do anything if it'll save Hina!
It's a quite ridiculous idea.
But...
Thank you.
Getting all depressed
just feels silly now.
-Because you're too idiotic.
-Eh?
Hey, now. Why you always
say stuff like that in the end?
But... why this happens even
after we saved Draken-kun?
I mean Mikey-kun and Draken-kun
is together now.
There should be no place for
Kisaki to worm his way in.
There's no way Toman get
this bad with Draken-kun around.
Checking out Ryuguji's curent
situation might worth the effort.
(To Naoto: -You know anything yet?
-What's going on right now?
-If you're alive, please say something~
-Hey....)
(Anything is fine.
If you learn something, contact me.)
(Tokyo Detention Center)
Sorry for the wait.
I haven't heard you in a while
so I was worried.
Sorry.
Anyway.
What are we here for?
(Tokyo Detention Center)
Number 248.
You've got visitors.
When I did my research...
I discovered that Ryuguji
isn't part of Toman in the present.
That said, there is also no
record of his death.
No wonder I can't find
him anywhere I look.
Right now, Ken Ryuguji...
...is on death row.
It has been a while, Takemicchi.
I'm glad you're okay.
Draken-kun!
Draken-kun.
Are you doing well?
Kind of.
Nice to meet you, I'm Naoto Tachibana.
It's thanks to this guy
I can visit you today.
I see.
So, what do you want?
I didn't know.
That you're on death row.
What happened?!
Why did you commit murder?
What happened to Toman?
Takemicchi.
I don't regret what I did.
And being here is just what I deserve.
It's my fault that Toman
became what it is now.
Because I couldn't stop him.
Him?
Toman, huh...
It was great when we were kids.
All we did was run around,
trying to make the gang bigger.
We brawled like crazy and
every day felt like a festival.
Toman was everything to me.
Even if I redo my life,
I'd choose to live the same way.
I have no regret.
As I thought, Draken-kun
is still Draken-kun!
He hasn't changed.
But...
But?
If I can really redo my life
one more time...
There is one thing I'd do no matter what.
I'd kill Kisaki!
Tetta Kisaki?!
You mean that Kisaki?!
Time's up.
Draken-kun!
Takemichi.
Get out of Tokyo.
Eh?
You nearly got killed, didn't you?
That's why you came here.
To Kisaki, killing people is no
different from squashing bugs.
Please wait!
Why?! Why would anyone
want to kill me?!
Draken-kun!
Kisaki adored Mikey.
But before we knew it,
that changed into hatred.
Kisaki...
He wants to take away
everything Mikey holds dear.
Kisaki...
Mikey-kun...
Draken-kun.
Good job.
Kisaki...
I can't believe Draken-kun's
on death row.
I'd kill Kisaki!
Naoto.
Just what kind of guy is Kisaki?
Tetta Kisaki.
In the current Tokyo Manji Gang,
he holds one of the most important
position as acting president.
He's likely the one responsible
for the repeated murder of my sister.
The police are pouring all their
effort into the investigation,
but we can't find any lead.
I haven't met him even once in the past.
Even if I want to go beat him,
we don't even know where he is.
Naoto.
As I thought, there's only one way.
I will become the top member of Toman!
You were serious?!
Yes! I'm really serious about this!
If I become the top member of Toman,
I can stop Kisaki.
I can also protect everyone including
Draken, Mikey, and Hina.
Our old ways was not good enough.
We must go to the root.
I've thought it over.
First, I'll become a captain.
Now that Pah-chin is gone,
the spot for 3rd squad captain is open.
I'll aim for that.
That's an extremely reckless idea.
But Naoto...
I don't think there is anything
else we can do.
I understand.
All things considered, you've somehow
succeeded in the mission thus far.
I trust you.
Seems like it will be
a long trip this time.
Yeah.
Why did I end up dumping Hina?
Why was Hanma there
when Hina was killed?
Why did Draken-kun end
up in a death row?
And who exactly is Kisaki?
How did he come to hate Mikey so much?
The mysteries scattered
like puzzle pieces.
I'll snap them together
and tear it apart!
All white?
Eh?
A bath house?
Boo!
M-Mikey-kun?!
You're that surprised?
Hey, pipe down!
Stop acting like a little kid.
Quit screwin' around
in the bath house.
Draken-kun?!
I don't want to hear that from a
guy who still uses shampoo hat
in his 3rd year of mid-school!
Hilarious, right?
A big guy like him is afraid of
getting shampoo in his eyes.
Shut up!
What's going on?!
I'm palling around in the bath house
with Mikey-kun and Draken-kun?!
Man, I feel alive again.
Draken-kun, are your
injuries healed yet?
Huh? They were no big deal.
'Cause I work out.
I see...
Here, look.
My abs, and scar.
You don't look like a middle
schooler at all. Scar included.
I know, right?
You haven't completely healed yet,
so don't push yourself.
What was that for, you bastard?!
Stop screwing around, you shit!
Whether I'm healed or not
is not the problem here!
That hurts!
What are you doing?!
Now you did it! Take this!
That's my two-in-one shampoo!
-Why are you trying to be fancy and stuff?!
-That's dangerous!
Stop it!
-Hey, that's mine!
-Fly away!
Takemicchi, you sure always got
stuff on top of your head.
I remember! The poop!
Just like what we expect
from you, Takemicchi.
But you should go die for once!
How dare you! Get off me!
-You're the one who started this!
-Shut up!
It was great when we were kids.
It will be great if things
could stay like this forever.
-Huh?!
Well...
Let's get out now.
Let's go, Takemicchi.
Eh? Go where?
'Bout time.
Takemicchi, let's go.
To the new 3rd squad captain
nomination ceremony.
Eh?!
A sword is perfect for
an earnest fella like you
You're a hero with no fire
You are weak and powerless
in front of a gun
It's not something to take lightly
Just try it, just try it, just try it
There is no correct answer
Mayday
Just a no no,
for a lazy lazy head
Look, for a fast and furious
Be-bop lifestyle
Stagnate, daydream, it's bad no no NO
An obvious pray to god,
bye bye to next life
Your number of excuse is wonder
Vomiting prejudice and urge
Most emotions are soda
Say it
Just a no no,
for a lazy lazy head
Look, for a fast and furious
Be-bop lifestyle
Stagnate, daydream, it's bad no no NO
Goodbye bye bye to next life