You guys listen up!
This person sitting behind me!
He's the new 3rd Squad Captain!
Tetta Kisaki!
Hey, hey, what is going on?
Looks like this is getting interesting.
What are you doing here, Baji?
You've been banned from our
gatherings for causing that infight.
Since I ruined your precious gathering,
will you finally kick me out this time?
What? What is this guy talking about?
You don't need troublemaker, right?
Mikey.
Baji!
I quit.
From now on, Keisuke Baji,
the 1st Squad Captain...
...will be Toman's enemy!
I have a favor for you, Takemicchi.
Yes.
Bring Baji back from Valhalla for me.
Can you do that for me?
Yes!
If it's for you, of course!
But...
Can I also ask just one thing from you?
Kisaki...
Please expel him from Toman.
Okay.
We will clash with Valhalla soon enough.
Your job is to get Baji back before then.
Prove that you're more useful than Kisaki.
Let's hurry!
Hey, don't run in the hallway!
Bring Baji back from Valhalla for me.
And if you fail...
I'll kill you.
What should I do?
Takemichi!
We heard the news.
So you became a member of Toman?
Akkun...
Hm? What's wrong?
You don't look so happy.
Eh?
Ah, th-that's right.
I became a member of Toman.
Just turned out that way.
Really? So what happened?
I can't look directly at Akkun!
The "Crybaby Takemichi" is now a Toman, huh.
Wish we could join, too.
It's not as good as you'd think.
We got our collars grabbed
and took an intense punch
After we got beaten up
Together we crouched
The anticipated rain came
“This should clean your bruise”
you lied with a smile
Even though you're
bad at argument
So stop making such lame jokes
It's so bad I teared up
Getting blue bruises all the time
I cry, cry, and cry
Leaning our unstable heart together
We fight against the rotten Bad End
I wonder why
The pleasant pain was more vivid,
even more than the happiness
Clicking our tongue over our wet clothes
We look at each other's faces and laugh
The Revenge we swore in that rainy night
I see.
So unless you get that former 1st Squad
Captain named Baji-kun from Valhalla,
Mikey-kun will kill you?
Yeah.
And I only got time until
Toman's fight with Valhalla starts.
But no telling when
will that happen, right?
It can even be today.
May you rest in peace, Takemichi.
I will pick up your bones.
To be honest, I don't know anything
about the situation inside Toman.
Much less anything about Valhalla.
Hey, Gang Dex.
Huh?
Well, if you insist.
Let me explain!
Tokyo Manji Gang, Toman for short.
Mikey-kun is the President
and Draken-kun is the Vice-President.
Under them are five squads.
Each squad has around 20 guys each.
They're a large Bosozoku
with 100 members total.
You know this much, right?
Wow. I didn't know that.
For real?
And you call yourself a delinquent?
Sorry.
Make sure you take a note.
This will be on the exam!
There! No chitchat!
He's totally on the role.
From what I've heard.
The former 3rd Squad Captain,
Pah-chin-kun got arrested.
And the Vice-Captain, Peh-yan-kun,
joined the 2nd Squad.
Eh? So Peh-yan-kun is
under Mitsuya-kun now?
Yeah.
We're in the same squad?!
I can't really handle being with him.
Takemicchi!
His voice scares me.
And, in exchange,
the new 3rd Squad Captain is...
Kisaki!
Yes! The former Moebius member.
Moebius wasn't exactly one
solid group to begin with.
Apparently, there was tension between
Osanai's group, those born in 1998
and Kisaki's group, those born in 1990.
Hmm, I see.
I suppose a gang got
a lot going on inside them.
After Osanai lost to Mikey-kun,
Moebius is essentially disbanded.
Then, the 1990 group led
by Kisaki joined Toman.
Making Toman's numbers
jump from 100 to 150.
That makes Kisaki's 3rd Squad
way bigger than any others in Toman.
Toman needs Kisaki's strength
to move forward.
What about the 1988 group
who was with Osanai?
The remaining 88' and 89'
have gathered...
Under Shuji Hanma.
That guy?
He did say he was Moebius's temporary
president during the battle of 8/3.
And Hanma gathered ex-Moebius members
along with anti-Toman force
to make a new gang named...
Valhalla.
Valhalla currently has 300 members!
300 members...
And Hanma is Valhalla's leader?
Hanma is the "acting president."
No one knows the real president.
The "face" of the President does not exist.
That's why people call Valhalla
as "The Headless Angel."
And Baji-kun joined that kind of gang?
To bring Baji-kun back to Toman.
I've got no choice but to
meet him in person.
But how?
Done.
Hey, you two.
Do you know what class
the 2nd-year Hanagaki is in?
-Eh?
-He is in class 3.
Hmm...
Thank you.
Since when we have such
a hottie in our school?
Going by his school shoe color,
he's a 3rd-year, right?
The ex-Moebius member are
under Hanma, Valhalla's No.2.
And the anti-Toman forced are under...
The No.3, Kazutora Hanemiya.
Eh?
Is school over already?
Who the hell are you?
You don't look familiar.
That's not very polite.
I'm actually your senior in this school.
Huh? Who are you?
Never seen you before.
That tiger tattoo on his neck!
Stop it, Makoto! This guy is...!
Huh? What is it?
Hey, you guys know Takemichi Hanagaki?
T-Takemichi...
That's him.
Huh?
Takemichi?
Th-This guy here is Valhalla's No.3!
Kazutora Hanemiya!
(Valhalla No.3 - Kazutora Hanemiya)
I'm so happy!
I had no idea there was someone
in Toman one grade below mine!
Okay, Takemichi!
-Eh?
-Let's go to Valhalla's hideout.
Huh? Valhalla?!
Hey! I found Takemichi!
Huh?
So that's the guy?
Yub.
Wh-Who are these guys?
Hmm? My most trusted junior.
I-I see...
Did anything happen?
They both on crutches...
Huh? I broke 'em yesterday.
Eh?!
But they're your most
trusted juniors, right?
Yeah.
You got a problem with Kazutora-kun?
No...
How can they be so calm
about having their legs broken?
In any case, this guy is
definitely a bad news!
Hurry up, Takemichi!
Valhalla's No.3, Kazutora Hanemiya.
Isn't it a bad idea to go
along with this guy?
We're going to the enemy's hideout!
Just relax!
I'll introduce you to everyone.
Everyone?
Could this be a chance to meet Baji-kun?!
But... I'm kinda scared.
Do you want to go to that
store I talked about before?
Yeah, let's go!
-I wonder what to eat today.
-Let's see...
Hina...
I want to eat perfait!
Sounds good!
I promised back then.
That I'll do anything to protect you.
Valhalla's hideout.
Bring it on!
If I can bring Baji-kun back to Toman,
Mikey-kun promised me that
he will expel Kisaki.
As long as I can get
Kisaki out of Toman...
The future will change!
I won't let that future
happen ever again!
Watch me!
Hina!
Who lets you walk around here?
Um...
Hanemiya-kun.
Hmm?
Just call me Kazutora.
Kazutora-kun.
You're a third-year at our school, right?
Yeah.
Umm...
I just figured everyone would
make a big deal knowing someone
as famous as you been
in our school all this time.
I only went for one semester as a first-year.
Eh?
I've been going to reform school.
Eh?!
Reform school...
You got arrested?
It was his fault.
Look, we're almost there.
His?
Who is he talking about?
Anyway, I must sneak into
Valhalla and take Baji-kun back!
Eh? In here?
Yub.
The arcade?
Already closed down
a long time ago, though.
(No Trespassing)
Headless angel...
The atmosphere here is clearly
different from Toman.
Eh?
Baji-kun?!
Kazutora-kun...
What's going on here?
What do you mean?
It's a loyalty test.
Loyalty test?
We're testing Baji's belief.
If he wants to "switch religion"
from Toman to Valhalla,
he needs to show he's truly ready for it.
The guy Baji is punching right now
is Toman's 1st Squad Vice-Captain.
Baji's most trusted retainer.
1st Squad Vice-Captain?!
Toman is Valhalla's enemy.
If he's betraying his old "God," Mikey
then he needs to stomp his old beliefs.
Well?
Is this good enough for you, Hanma-kun?
For my initiation into Valhalla.
(Sin & Punishment)
You sure are something.
He was with you for a long time, right?
I'm impressed you can go that far.
What?
I didn't come here to
listen to some dumb lectures.
Kazutora.
Yeah?
Did you get him?
Yeah, this one.
He's Takemichi Hanagaki.
Toman's new member.
Eh?!
Am I gonna be...
...the next "loyalty test?"
So you're Hanagaki?
Step forward.
C'mon.
You're from that time?
You came here to get killed?
Kill him!
Kill him! Kill him!
I came to bring Baji-kun back.
But now Baji-kun will kill me?
One of Toman's founding members
and the 1st Squad Captain, Keisuke Baji!
He claims he wants to abandon
Toman and join Valhalla!
One of Toman's top-brass
wants to join Valhalla?
Ain't that bad?
No, this is a huge deal.
Indeed!
This is a very serious matter!
Enlisting Baji will aid us
greatly in crushing Toman!
But!
We must first solve just
one remaining problem.
He might be one of Toman's spies!
So I had Kazutora
prepare a witness for us!
I will now summon the witness forward!
Takemichi Hanagaki.
Y-Yes?
What did Baji over here say in
front of everyone at Toman's gathering?
Well..
"I'm joining Valhalla."
"Toman is my enemy."
That's what he said.
Kazutora, what do you think?
"Loyalty test" and "Witness summon."
I think that's good enough.
We can use Baji in a fight.
And he knows a lot about
Toman while I was away.
I believe it's worth
letting him join Valhalla.
Are you sure, Baji?
We will crush Toman.
And then...
We'll kill Mikey.
Yeah.
I'll help you with that.
Kazutora.
That's enough, right?
Okay!
From this day forward, Keisuke Baji
is a member of Valhalla!
No way...
This is bad!
I'll never be able to get
Baji-kun back at this rate!
Please wait a minute!
Baji-kun, you helped found Toman
alongside Mikey-kun and the rest, right?
How can you betray them?!
I won't betray Toman because
I'm a founding member?
What a joke.
That guy is a founding member too.
The 6th guy in that picture!
So that was Kazutora-kun?!
Kazutora resented Toman.
I can never forget.
In 2003.
That summer of our first year
of middle school.
We ran wild.
It was a bit chilly for a mid-summer day.
You got called out by Mikey, too?
Yeah.
Same place as usual, right?
(Baji - Age 12)
Give us your money!
Please stop...
-Ah.
-Eh?
Sorry.
We got late.
(Kazutora - Age 12)
Baji hit some punks.
Hey, don't blame it all on me!
Whoa! So cool!
Oh, what is it?
Toman's Tokko-fuku is done!
(Pah-chin - Age 12)
Oh, awesome!
Right?!
The decoration is so detailed!
This rocks, Mitsuya!
Don't give me that.
(Mitsuya - Age 13)
I'm the one pushed to make 'em.
Alright!
Let's change into 'em and
take a commemorative picture!
(Draken - Age 13)
Right, Mikey?
(Mikey - Age 12)
Hm?
Ah! You bastard!
Why'd you eat all my chocolate parfait?!
Whoops, didn't notice.
You said you only wanted a bite!
You can just order another one.
That's not the problem here!
What do you mean?
I wanted to eat THIS chocolate parfait!
-Aaah.
-What is it?!
You sure are persistent, huh.
Huh?! You bastards!
-I'll beat--
-Thank you for the food!
Argh, fine!
Hey!
H-Here goes.
Hurry up!
Y-Yes.
Say cheese!
I never could have imagined
the incident that happened next.
A sword is perfect for
an earnest fella like you
You're a hero with no fire
You are weak and powerless
in front of a gun
It's not something to take lightly
Just try it, just try it, just try it
There is no correct answer
Mayday
Just a no no,
for a lazy lazy head
Look, for a fast and furious
Be-bop lifestyle
Stagnate, daydream, it's bad no no NO
An obvious pray to god,
bye bye to next life
Your number of excuse is wonder
Vomiting prejudice and urge
Most emotions are soda
Say it
Just a no no,
for a lazy lazy head
Look, for a fast and furious
Be-bop lifestyle
Stagnate, daydream, it's bad no no NO
Goodbye bye bye to next life