I didn't expect my life
would end up like this.
I live in a beat-up apartment
with thin walls.
My manager who's younger
than me treats me like an idiot.
Even kids made fun of me,
and I had to apologize for them.
I've only ever got one girlfriend in life,
and that was back in middle school.
Just where did I go wrong?
Eh?
No way...
Who is this lame delinquent?
It's me! It's me from middle school!
So lame!
I'm hungry
I wanna eat some katsudon.
What's wrong, Takemichi?
Sorry, I gotta go.
Eh? Go where?!
Yes?
Eh? Hanagaki-kun?
Did you get into a fight again?
You shouldn't go fighting
all the time, you know?
Eh?
Are you one of my sister's friends?
Naoto Tachibana.
That's right. This guy will die
in the next 12 years, too.
On July 1st, 12 years from now on,
your sister... will die.
And you will die with
her at the same time.
July 1st, 2017.
Remember that date, Naoto.
And protect your sister.
I understand.
Please help me out.
I'm sure you can save my sister!
I can...
...save Tachibana?
Time leap.
I have my own theory on
how your power works.
You jumped from July 4th, 2017 in
the present to July 4th, 2005 in the past.
In other words, you can return to
the same day 12 years in the past.
I believe that's the power that you have.
We got our collars grabbed
and took an intense punch
After we got beaten up
Together we crouched
The anticipated rain came
“This should clean your bruise”
you lied with a smile
Even though you're bad at argument
So stop making such lame jokes
It's so bad I teared up
Getting blue bruises all the time
I cry, cry, and cry
Leaning our unstable heart together
We fight against the rotten Bad End
I wonder why
The pleasant pain was more vivid,
even more than the happiness
Clicking our tongue over our wet clothes
We look at each other's face and laugh
The Revenge we swore in that rainy night
I'm sleepy.
That part is important.
Did you read that part properly?
And this, too.
You went too far.
Yes, there. Remember that, too.
Two days has passed since then.
I'm confined inside Naoto's room
and haven't slept since.
I'll teach you everything there is
to know about Tokyo Manji Gang.
Naoto is crazy.
He's planning to kill me.
Five days ago on July 1st.
Hinata Tachibana got caught in a dispute
between the criminal organization,
Tokyo Manji Gang and died.
During the day of the festival,
a truck hit the stall she was in and die.
She was 26 years old at that time.
You can find detail about the
Tokyo Manji Gang's actions
that has yet been disclosed
to the public in that repot.
My predecessor risked his life
to investigate it.
The one in that last picture is him.
Eh?
His cover was blown during
the investigation and they killed him.
His eyeballs... were scoop open.
And a device that recorded the entire
thing were found inside his eye socket.
After countless request,
I was able to be left in charge
of this investigation half a year ago.
The police decided to keep this a secret
to avoid commotion in the general public.
The name of the investigator is omitted.
Even before this, the Tokyo Manji Gang
is primarily led by Tetta Kisaki.
Naoto is trying to teach me everything
he knows about the Tokyo Manji Gang.
But is this really necessary
to save Tachibana?
The issue with your ability is that you can
only go to the current date 12 years in the past.
That was just your theory, wasn't it?
But you're alive right now.
So what happens back then was real.
But how am I supposed to
back to the past again--
If you back to the day my sister died!
And stop her from going to
the festival by force,
we might be able to save her.
But since we can't choose
when in the past we can go,
we must do what we can do right now.
Please use the time leap,
go back to 12 years ago during
your middle school days,
and meet a certain person.
A certain person?
The two leaders of Toman.
Manjiro Sano and Tetta Kisaki.
Scary.
Sano and Kisaki.
If these two hadn't met, the current
Tokyo Manji Gang wouldn't exist.
In other words, my sister wouldn't
get caught in their action and die.
I see.
So I have to go back to
my middle school days
and prevent them
from meeting each other.
I understand the plan, but how
do I get back to the past again?
Takemichi-kun, you told me you got back
when you shook hand with me, right?
Oh? Yeah.
That might be the trigger.
So it was that handshake?
That time, you saved me.
And because of that, I might
have become part of your power.
I see.
I thought he was some
kind of a crazy dude at first.
But he's this serious precisely because
he believes that I can leap through time.
Takemichi-kun.
Are you ready?
When it comes to the desire to
save Tachibana...
Yeah.
I won't lose to Naoto!
Sano and Kisaki.
They both met each other
in August, 12 years ago.
Get in contact with either one of them,
follow their movement,
and stop them from meeting each other.
Okay, I'll do my best.
You're the only one
who can save my sister.
Let's do this!
Eh? Where's Naoto?
Stop stallin' you idiot!
-Hurry up!
-Kill him!
Eh? Hold on...
Did you come here to eat breakfast?!
Don't put me to sleep, you dumbass!
C'mon, do it!
Hanagaki, I bet 1000 yen on you!
What the heck is going on?!
Hold on a second!
(Wednesday, July 6th, 2005)
I'm in 12 years in the past!
It's just as Naoto said!
Wait, hold on--
I really leaped through time again.
Hey, Hanagaki is awake.
Did I pass out?
Why did you get knocked
out in one punch, dumbass?!
Everyone bet money on you.
Don't show us a lame-ass match like that.
Match?
Ain't that right, Kiyomasa?
That scar on his eyebrow.
The leader of Shibuya Third Mid.
Masataka Kiyomizu!
This underground fight is over
if there's no one to watch.
Underground fight?
I see.
People were betting money
on that fight.
I remember now.
These guys were a bookie.
For now, teach that piece of shit a lesson.
What are you, a freaking turtle?
Stand up, you shit!
I'll beat some guts out of you!
That's right!
I was their slave!
I was forced to do what they told me.
What the heck's wrong with this turtle?
Leave me some spot to hit too, Red.
There!
What a lame nerd!
They force me to fight some random guy.
And if I lose they will beat me up.
Every single day.
It was a living hell.
That's why I ran.
O-Ouch...
I abandoned my friends and
even my girlfriend, Tachibana.
Tachibana...
You better try a little harder next time.
You were so pathetic today.
Let's go.
Wanna eat some ramen?
Umm...
Man, you're persistent.
You're still awake?
Umm...
You guys are in
the Tokyo Manji Gang, right?
I'd like to meet the leaders,
like Sano or Kisaki...
So I wonder if you could help me out...
Ah, if that's not possible,
then that's okay.
Bring me my bat.
S-Sorr--
H-Hey, shouldn't we stop him now?
Kiyomasa! Stop it! He will die!
Wake up, Hanagaki.
The next time Sano-kun's name
comes out of your mouth...
Do you know what will happen?
I will kill you.
SCARY!!
What's wrong with this guy?!
You can't even talk with him!
It's impossible! I can't meet them!
He said he'll kill me if I say their name!
I'll seriously die at this rate!
Is this guy seriously a middle schooler?
Meeting the leaders of the Tokyo Manji Gang?
A slave like me?
It's impossible!
It's impossible, Naoto!
I forgot.
I completely forgot.
I'm still me.
It won't change even in
my second chance at life.
Let's go back.
Back to the future.
How can I go back?
That's right.
Our handshake is the trigger.
I just have to meet Naoto.
Eh? Is no one at home?
It has to be Naoto.
As long I can shake my hand with
Naoto, I can return to the future.
You're the only one
who can save my sister.
Am I going to run away again?
Eh?
Hanagaki-kun?
Tachibana? Why?
Why you ask?
That's my house.
I see.
Well, of course--
Did you get in a fight again?
Sorry.
You look really bad today.
Are you okay?
Umm, yeah.
I'm totally fine.
Why do boys always get into a fight?
If only I were a boy, too.
And then... Eiyah!
I will protect you.
I trained in Karate, so if I were a boy,
I'd be really strong.
In that case...
I will also protect you, Hina.
Ah...
I accidentally called her Hina...
Okay!
Ah, well, I got caught in the moment...
I like it that way.
But I'll be the one to protect you, okay?
What?
Because you're a crybaby, Takemichi-kun.
If I'm a boy, I'd definitely
be stronger than you.
C'mon, that ain't true!
I only cried that one time, okay?
Was it?
Forget it!
No, I won't!
Bye bye! See you tomorrow.
Yeah!
I'm home!
In 12 years in the future...
I'm not dating Hina anymore,
and I haven't seen her in years.
I have no obligation to save Hina.
I will protect you.
But...
She...
She shouldn't die!
Takemichi!
Takuya?
Why did you lose to a guy like him?
That just ain't like you.
Eh? Aaah...
The yesterday's fight?
Sorry.
Hey.
Come here.
They said they will be doing
the underground fight again today.
They've been doing it nearly every day.
He said the fighter today is Takuya.
Takuya Yamamoto.
His body is weak.
If I remember correctly,
he nearly died that day.
Takuya can't do it!
He's not good at fighting!
Say that to Kiyomasa-kun.
Can you do it?
If I could take his place, I would.
Akkun...
He tried to cover up for Takuya...
They won't listen to what others say.
Akkun...
Thank you, Akkun.
I couldn't do anything.
Takemichi.
Eh?
Watch me.
I will avenge you.
Treat me some gyudon if I win.
Takuya...
Dammit!
Anyway, keep your spirit up, okay?
Yeah, I know.
Do your best, Takuya--
Wash your hand first, Magishi.
That was close.
I nearly touch you like that.
I thought they were lame.
But they're actually very cool.
So I had such great friends like
them back in middle school.
-Let's go!
-Yeah!
Don't be too tense or
you will fart yourself.
That's just you.
Takemichi, hurry up.
Ah, yeah.
Greetings to all gentlemen
who have gathered here!
The competitors today are
just as it said in the email!
We have Kojima from Sakura Mid!
Yeah~!
Don't "Yeah" us you dumbass!
Don't you get carried away, baldy!
If you lose I'll make you go
home in your underwear!
And Yamamoto from Mizo Mid!
Die, you long haired bastard!
Don't piss your pants, you shit!
The odds are 4 to 6 slightly
in Kojima's favor.
Give it your all, Yamada!
It's Yamamoto.
I bet 500 yen on ya!
If ya lose, I'll be bankrupt!
Don't ya dare to lose, dumbass!
Alright, come on.
I'll chop you into three pieces.
Begin.
WAIT--!!!
T...Takemichi?!
The heck are you doing?
Who's this guy?
2nd year should just shut the hell up!
Huh? 2nd year?
Well, ain't it boring to watch the same
type of match every single time?
Don't cha want to watch
something more interesting?
Didn't you get your ass beaten
in one punch yesterday?
Get outta here, you buffoon!
Something more interesting?
I have to fight.
F-For example...
I mustn't run away.
Who the hell are you?
Don't get in our way!
H-Hey...
Takemichi...
King versus slave.
Hey hey hey, this guy is nuts!
The heck is he saying?
What do you mean by that?
Takemichi...
Could he be...
Kiyomasa-senpai.
Fight me one-on-one.
Both in the past and the future.
I have to change myself, or else,
I can't change anything.
I won't run anymore!
I just want to be right next to you
Next to your slightly sweaty shirt
The rain falls all of the sudden
So I gave you a kiss in that lonely night
If you look back, I will always
be there and smiling at you
Please
Give up on that unachievable future
Take it now
In the real new world
If I have to give you a name,
it's "My Hero"
That straight wish
Will go beyond the stopped time
"I don't need anyone but you"
I will keep living here
Break down that crooked needle
Shout out that firm words
Kick away that unmeaning destiny