I must meet the leaders of
the Tokyo Manji gang.
Both Sano and Kisaki!
We got our collars grabbed
and took an intense punch
After we got beaten up
Together we crouched
The anticipated rain came
"This should clean your bruise"
you lied with a smile
Even though you're bad at argument
So stop making such lame jokes
It's so bad I teared up
Getting blue bruises all the time
I cry, cry, and cry
Leaning our unstable heart together
We fight against the rotten Bad End
I wonder why
The pleasant pain was more vivid,
even more than the happiness
Clicking our tongue over our wet clothes
We look at each other's face and laugh
The Revenge we swore in that rainy night
I'll never be able to meet
them if I keep on being a slave!
You better not regret this.
I can't win.
Our difference in power was so big,
I can tell it in an instant.
What's wrong, Hanagaki?
Are you just all talk?
You better not get one-hit
KO'd like last time!
Takemichi!
That's enough, Takemichi!
Give up or you will die!
I'm not done yet!
Kill him, Kiyomasa-kun!
Finish him!
Kiyomasa...
Not yet...
I'm not over yet!
That's enough, Takemichi!
You will seriously die!
Takemichi, stop this already!
Not yet!
This is not enough.
To heal...
...my broken heart...
...that has been through those 12 years!
What the heck is he saying?
I ran... I ran...
I ran and ran...
You're the only one
who can save my sister.
Give up already, Takemichi!
You already showed enough of your spirit!
I ain't giving up!
I have a reason to not give up!
Tokyo Manji Gang...
Kiyomasa...
The only way to win is to kill me!
I definitely won't lose!
I...
I will save Hina!
Bring me my bat!
This is bad!
We must go save Takemichi!
Fine by me!
I will kill you.
Did he say bat?
Isn't this supposed to be one-on-one?
Hurry up and bring me my bat, you shits!
Oi, Kiyomasa.
You're creeping the crowd.
Who's it?
Why are you getting so worked up?
You're the host here.
A blond braid...
And a dragon tattoo on his temple...
No way...
The vice-president of the Tokyo Manji Gang...
Ken Ryuguji!
(Tokyo Manji Gang Vice-president - Ken Ryuguji)
Also known as Draken!
Hey hey, Ken-chin.
Hah?
Don't call me by that
nickname at a place like this.
All my Dorayaki's gone.
What the hell is up with that guy?
He can't read the atmosphere at all.
Good work!
Could he be...!
Good work, President!
(Tokyo Manji Gang President - Manjiro Sano)
The leader of the Tokyo
Manji Gang, Manjiro Sano!
Sano-kun!
I'm Akaishi from the 3rd Squad!
You're in the way.
Mikey ain't talking to a guy
he's not interested in.
I... I'm sorry.
Is this real?
Even that Red-kun can't
say anything back at him!
Good work.
Kiyomasa, since when you
become so important?
You're seriously greeting the president
with that shallow bow?
I-I understand.
What's your name?
T-Takemichi... Hanagaki.
I see.
Takemicchi.
Eh? Takemicchi?
That's what Mikey said,
so that's what is right, Takemicchi.
Eh?
Are you seriously a middle schooler?
Takemicchi, you're now my buddy, okay?
Eh?
Are you the host?
Ah, yes.
Who the heck are you?
Kiyomasa...
Well then...
Let's go home, Ken-chin.
Underground fights are stupid.
Don't do things that ruin
the name of Toman.
Takemicchi.
See ya later.
Don't just stand there.
Go away already.
So he's the boss of Toman, Manjiro Sano.
You were awesome, Takemichi!
I was deeply moved!
Eh?
You got that invincible Mikey to like you!
You're amazing, Takemichi!
As I thought...
I got myself liked by that monster!
Lick it.
-Yes, Master!
-I just went from being Kiyomasa's slave
to a toy of monster I can't understand!
It's just another hell!
Why it must be me?!
From today onward,
you're Takemicchi, got it?
That's what Mikey said,
so that's what is right, Takemicchi.
Idiots sure have it easy.
They sure are idiots, aren't they?
Mmn? Yeah.
But it's been long since last time
I saw them acting like idiots.
Takemichi.
I....
...actually tried to stab Kiyomasa-kun.
Eh?
Think about it.
If things stay as they were, we'd
spend the rest of our lives as slaves.
We'd have no choice but to kill him.
Akkun...
You do care about your friends a lot.
Thank you, Takemichi.
Eh?
Thanks to your hard work, we're
finally freed from being slaves.
You were really cool.
Cut it out, you're making me blush.
Yamagishi! You don't even sound like him!
Shut up, Takemicchi!
School sure is a pain in the ass.
Why eighth in the morning?
It's too early!
Morning, Takemichi-kun!
Hina!
You're going to school in
the morning! Good boy!
I'll be going to cram school
this afternoon.
Oh, is that so?
Let's have a date on
our way to cram school.
Oh, okay.
So you would even call that a date?
Going to school together is also a date.
Aaaah, if only I'm in
the same class as you.
School is the best!
This part is important.
Make sure you remember this.
But still, it's not the time to
be happy about it.
Tetta Kisaki and Manjiro Sano.
Stop them from meeting each other.
If you can do that,
my sister will be saved.
Naoto... I met Manjiro Sano.
By coincidence, though.
In order to save Hina who got
caught and died in their mess,
I must stop Tokyo Manji Gang's dispute.
And to do that, I must prevent the two
leaders of Touman from meeting each other!
I somehow managed to meet
one of the leaders, Manjiro Sano.
But I have no idea
what to do from now on!
Preventing them from meeting is really
difficult if you think about it, isn't it?
From what school are you?!
Don't just barge into someone's
school as you like!
Oh, there you are.
Eh?
Let's play, Takemicchi.
E-Erm, we're in middle of class...
This guy... is absurd!
A-All the 3rd years...
Umm, what's happening here?
Ah, this?
They pissed me off,
so I knocked 'em down.
All of you, line up right here.
Laying face down, okay?
Hey, too much space in-between.
It's you guys who will
get hurt from that.
Eh?
Just what are they gonna do?
The Tokyo Manji Gang
is crazy as I thought.
I heard the team from Udagawa is
making Shinsen their territory.
Sounds fun. Let's go beat them up.
Tormenting people is an
everyday occurrence for them!
To them, it's the same
as washing their face.
You feelin' good?
Well, last we met was yesterday.
You're free today, right?
Well... not exactly.
Let's hang out for a little.
Eh?
Mikey-kun, did you listen
to what I said?
Is he actually friends with Mikey?
We got someone that
amazing in this school?
Hey, isn't that Takemichi?
Didn't Mikey like him?
What did he do in these past few days?
This is bad, they will kill him!
Tachibana?
Mikey? As in Mikey from Toman?
Does that mean the other guy is Draken?
You're too loud. Do you want
them to beat you again?
-There's no need to be so tense.
-I see, this is a chance!
I just have to stay close to Mikey and
prevent him from meeting Tetta Kisaki.
-Let's go then.
-Hold it right there!
Who?
Hina?!
Sorry, turned out I had
something else to do today.
Takemichi-kun, let's go.
You mustn't let people
like them dictate you.
Eh?
I will protect you.
Hina...
She's trembling.
Hey.
Do you want me to kill you, bitch?
You gonna slap someone
and leave just like that?
Don't you play around with me!
Who's the one playing around here?
Coming to others' school
and take someone by force...
It's not what a friend would do!
Takemichi-kun have been getting
nothing but injuries lately.
If that was because of you guys...
I will not forgive you!
Huh?
Let go of her hand.
What are you saying? I can't hear you!
I will protect you.
I told you to let go of her hand, idiot!
I already promised that I will
protect Hina this time!
Do you know who you're talking to?
I ain't gonna give her up ever again!
Huh?
Again?
Aaaaah...
And here I thought we can
be great buddies. Too bad.
Well then...
How do you want to die?
Promise me....
Promise me this one thing!
Don't you dare lay your hand on Hina!
Huh? Who cares.
Just kidding.
Eh?
Takemicchi, you dummy.
There's no way I'd lay a hand on a girl.
Takemicchi.
You were trying to threaten me, huh?
S-Sorry...
It's fine.
Eh?
"I ain't gonna give her up."
No one says that in front of a girl
nowadays, you know?
You're so Showa.
You surprised me, you know.
Huh? Takemichi-kun...
Are they...
I'm very sorry!
I've misread the situation.
It's fine.
That was an amazing slap.
I'm sorry!
Doing your best for the sake of
someone you love is good and all,
but you mustn't do anything reckless.
Depending on who you're dealing with,
it might not end up good.
Yes!
I'll go now.
Ah, yeah.
Then what about our date?
We can do it in another day.
Your friends came all the way here
to play with you, after all.
Bye bye!
Don't slap me next time, okay?
What a good girl.
Girls like her are rare, you know.
You should treat her well.
I learned about the Tokyo Manji Gang
12 years in the future from Naoto.
They're a heinous gang who would
do gamble, fraud, assault, murder,
and a bunch of other crimes.
Underground fights are stupid.
There's no way I'd lay a hand on a girl.
Is this person really the leader
of that hideous Toman gang?
Umm, Mikey-kun.
Nnn?
Well...
Why did you take a liking
in someone like me?
What a stupid question.
Aah... I'm sorry.
I have a brother ten years older than me.
He's dead, though.
He was a reckless guy.
He'd pick a fight against someone
stronger than him like it's normal.
Ooh.
He sounds like a cool person.
You're like my older brother, Takemicchi.
Eh? N-No, I'm not as cool as him!
No matter how you look at me.
Well, true he wasn't as lame as you.
That's mean...
People call delinquents "lame"
in this era, isn't it?
I see... So that way of thinking
already spread even back now.
There were a lot of Bosozoku
back during my brother's era.
They'd ride through the street
with their loud pipes.
Everyone acted big.
All they do was fighting.
But they would always take
care of their own mess.
What was so lame about those guys?
That's why I'm going to create
an era for delinquents.
You should come with me.
I like your guts.
Takemichi Hanagaki.
There are plenty of guys who
are good at fighting.
But...
There aren't that many guys like you
who would stand against anyone
for what they can't give up.
Think about it, Takemicchi.
Mikey is a delinquent,
but he's not a bad guy.
At the very least, he's not the type of guy
who would drive a truck into a festival
and kill innocents like Hina.
He's definitely not the boss of an organization
like Tokyo Manji Gang 12 years in the future.
Just what changed Mikey?
Manjiro Sano and Tetta Kisaki.
If these two hadn't met, the current
Tokyo Manji Gang wouldn't exist.
Eh?
Mnn?
It feels like I have seen
him somewhere before.
I just want to be right next to you
Next to your slightly sweaty shirt
The rain falls all of the sudden
So I kissed you in that lonely night
If you look back, I will always
be there and smiling at you
Please
Give up on that unachievable future
Take it now
In the real new world
If I have to give you a name,
it's "My Hero"
That straight wish
Will go beyond the stopped time
"I don't need anyone but you"
I will keep living here
Break down that crooked needle
Shout out that firm words
Kick away that unmeaning destiny