Look at this picture, it's nuts!
Oh crap, it's really nuts!
Like legit nuts!
Seriously nuts!
Right?
So noisy.
Hey!
H-Hina?!
You're taking too much space.
It's fine when there isn't
anyone around.
But there's an old lady standing.
How about letting her sit?
Kay.
Scoot over.
Thank you.
-Cute!
-So cute.
Ma'am, there's a free seat over there.
Oh, thanks for all the trouble.
Hina... she's amazing.
We got our collars grabbed
and took an intense punch
After we got beaten up
Together we crouched
The anticipated rain came
"This should clean your bruise"
you lied with a smile
Even though you're bad at argument
So stop making such lame jokes
It's so bad I teared up
Getting blue bruises all the time
I cry, cry, and cry
Leaning our unstable heart together
We fight against the rotten Bad End
I wonder why
The pleasant pain was more vivid,
even more than the happiness
Clicking our tongue over our wet clothes
We look at each other's face and laugh
The Revenge we swore in that rainy night
Thank you for coming
to shop with me.
Yeah, don't mention it.
How did your finals go?
Oh, finals? That's so nostalgic!
Nostalgic?
But we just had them earlier.
Ah, yeah, that's true.
Crap, I said it out loud.
You should study properly.
You got a dream, don't you?
A dream?
Did I have a dream before?
Okay, I've decided.
I'll help you study.
What's wrong?
This is my first time being
inside a girl's room.
Don't look around that much.
Sorry.
You have no tact.
I'm sorry.
It was sudden so I didn't
have much to prepare.
Even though this is the first time
Hina brought a boy over.
-Mama!
-Don't worry about it.
What a cute boy.
How did you meet him?
Is he from the same class?
That's enough, Mama! Get out!
Eeeh?
-Is he your boyfriend?
-Mama!
I don't get this at all.
Ah, that's right.
Thank you for helping
out my brother.
He told me you saved
him from delinquents.
Our father is usually really busy,
so he rarely comes home.
Naoto said he hates him for that.
But now he suddenly says that
he wants to be like him someday.
Our dad is a police officer.
So that's why Naoto
became a police officer!
Eh?
But he isn't though.
He's still too young.
Y-Y-Yeah!
What am I even talking about!
But maybe, I'm the one
who was saved that day.
Eh?
I'm sure he will become a great
police officer one day.
Well, he might be a bit
crazy in some places.
You sure have changed, Takemichi-kun.
D-Do you think so?
In what way?
It's like you've become kinder,
or act more like an adult.
It's like I'm talking to someone
much older than me.
Really~?
She's sharp! I am 12 years older now!
I guess there are things that
I have yet to know about you.
Eh?
I want to know more
about you, Takemichi-kun.
Oh! Fireworks!
That's right! There's a
firework festival today!
Hey, let's watch them from the rooftop.
So pretty!
Hurry up, Takemichi-kun!
Crap, this is so much fun!
I never experienced this
in my previous life.
Whoa, it's heart shaped!
Hey, did you see that?
I want to stay here forever.
I don't want to go back to the future.
After all, in the future....
Hina... doesn't exist.
It should be okay to
hold her hand, right?
So warm.
Hina...
Nnn?
H-Hey...
Naoto?!
That handshake is the trigger.
Na... Naoto?!
Eh? You're here, too, Naoto?
Yeah.
You got to be kidding me!!!
Takemichi-kun!
Now I'm back...!
So that means you managed
to return to the past?
So our handshake is the trigger!
Just why were you there!
Eh? What are you talking about?
Anyway, my theory wasn't wrong!
Yeah, yeah, you were right.
And you've made it back.
Nnn?
I understand now...
about everything.
How about you?
You come back because you
made a progress, right?
Well...
You shook my hand on accident?!
Get yourself together!
I learned something from
your second time leap.
Oh?
Your ability to time leap allows you to
go to the same date 12 years in the past.
For example, if you were to
return to the past today,
you'd arrive at the same date 12 years ago.
And if you stay for a week
there and then return,
you would arrive in the present
a week after your departure.
And during your trip to the past,
your body is in suspended animation.
Eh? You mean I was dead?
It means your body that remains
in the present is an empty shell.
Oh, so that's why I was
in suspended animation?
It's dangerous, so next time you do
a time leap, let's do it in my room.
So, how did the mission to prevent
Sano and Kisaki from meeting go?
Well, I did meet Mikey-kun.
Mikey? Ah, you mean Sano?
Hear me out, Naoto!
Mikey is a delinquent,
but he's a good guy.
Huh?
Why didn't you kill him?
Eh? Kill?
The person who killed
my sister is a good guy?
Did he trick you into
believing that in the past?
-No!
-Listen up!
That "Mikey" guy is now a man who has
been involved in every crime imaginable
that even the police can't control!
If it's possible,
I'd like to kill him myself.
Naoto.
Let's go meet Mikey-kun.
It's dangerous!
I want to meet him in person
and ask him directly.
Whatever you say to him,
it's pointless.
Mikey-kun is a trustworthy person.
I want to ask Mikey's opinion
on why Toman changed.
I want to ascertain that
before I go back to the past.
Let's look for Mikey-kun together.
I beg you, Naoto.
I don't know what happened in the past.
But you sure have changed, Takemichi-kun.
Eh? You think so?
In what way?
You have become less frail.
Just by a little, though.
S-So you're saying I've become cool?
Well then, let's look for
a way to meet Mikey now.
Hey hey, or you're saying I'm hot now?
-Hey hey!
-Don't get so full of yourself.
Takemichi-kun, sort
through those documents.
The Tokyo Manji Gang is real nuts.
Mikey is a frighteningly cautious person.
Even the police haven't
gotten any leads on him.
The phone number he uses is
probably registered under a fake name.
Who is this?
Mnn?
One of the managers of Toman,
Atsushi Sendo!
It's Akkun!
Akkun? Is he your friend?
Yeah.
That's weird.
If it's him, when he was 16,
he should be arrested for stabbing
Masataka Kiyomizu from Toman,
and become a small-time hoodlum
after being released from prison.
I actually tried to stab Kiyomasa-kun.
He did say that!
Could it be...
Because the past was changed?!
Since Akkun didn't attack Kiyomasa-kun,
he didn't get arrested by the police.
And since you become close with Mikey...
So does Sendo?
Akkun is a manager in Toman?
Oh right!
Can you contact Sendo?
Eh? Yeah.
If he didn't change his phone number.
If Sendo Atsushi is a manager there,
then he might be able to contact Mikey.
It's dirty so you should prepare yourself.
Well, I can imagine.
So dirty!
I did tell you to prepare yourself.
How can someone even live here?
Just hold on for a minute.
I'm gonna look for the memo
book I used a long time ago.
Ouch.
The house dust is giving me the hives!
I'll go buy masks.
Yeah yeah, go run for it!
(Secret)
Ah, found it!
This is it!
Whoa, so nostalgic!
All those memories are coming back!
Who was this guy? So nostalgic!
Can you please hurry up?
Ah, yeah.
Akkun, right?
I got it, okay.
Found him.
Let's hope he didn't change his number.
Akkun...
See you guys tomorrow.
See ya!
Man, my body hurts all over the places.
Hey, Akkun.
If we all go to our separate ways
after graduating and stop meeting up...
What do you think we'll talk
about after becoming adults?
Nothing will change, dumbass.
Eh?
We will always be friends.
You think Sendo is here?
Yeah.
He told me this is the hostess
club he runs right now.
Is it really safe to just show up
here nonchalantly?
Sendo is one of the manager
in Toman right now.
Touman's manager or not,
Akkun is still Akkun.
He does sound a bit
older on the phone,
but he's still the same as always.
I'm concerned that you told him
that we're looking for Mikey.
Why?
You're being too frank.
Not even the police can
get close to this guy.
We might get killed inside.
Naoto, you're such a dummy!
Real friendship won't change that easily.
Just shut up and follow me!
Welcome! Who would you like to pick?
Eh? Ah, ermm...
Are you okay?
W-We're here to meet
up with Sendo-san.
Huh? You? With our president?
Hey! Some shabby-looking guy is here!
Did the president have appointment today?
Oh jeez! You should've just
say so earlier, Hanagaki-san!
If we know you were president's friend,
we would let you go see him immediately!
Two VIPs coming in!
He's making fun of he, isn't he?
Nah, no way.
Your hand is trembling, Takemichi-kun.
It's not because I'm scared!
It's okay!
No matter how much his
social status changed...
No matter how distinguished
he has become...
Akkun is still Akkun!
Takemichi.
Behind you.
You haven't changed at all, Takemichi.
(Tokyo Manji Gang Manager - Atsushi Sendo)
Akkun!
Didn't recognize me without
my pompadour, huh?
Yeah.
I thought about calling you earlier.
But it was so nostalgic seeing
you so I didn't.
It's Akkun!
He looks completely different,
but he's still Akkun!
So you want to meet Mikey-san?
I've been waiting for you, too.
Takemichi.
What do you mean?
Let's talk about this outside.
Just the two of us.
Is it okay?
I will be waiting here.
Be careful.
It's fine.
There's no need to worry.
Have you been doing well, Takemichi?
T-T-T-That hurts, Akkun!
I'm just so happy to meet
you after so long!
A lot of time has gone by!
You remember that time with Yamagishi?
When he farted and
ruined the whole thing?
Yes!
Man, even though I was
so in the zone then!
You were really lame that time.
It's been since middle school, huh?
Yeah.
I suppose it has been 10 years
from your perspective.
But man, you're amazing, Akkun.
You're the owner of a huge hostess club.
And you're a manager in Toman, right?
Yeah...
You get to drive the best car,
wear the best clothes,
and sleep with the best woman.
You're living in a completely
different world from me.
There's a limit in how much stuff
you can get with money.
Man, I really want to be able to say that.
The guy you're with is
a police officer, right?
Eh?
Well...
You don't have to hide it. It's obvious.
He's Hinata Tachibana's
little brother, isn't he?
I didn't know she had a little brother.
Why do you know about that?
The Tokyo Manji Gang is that
type of organization.
Hey, do you remember?
Summer, our second middle school year.
That day you rebelled
against Kiyomasa-kun.
After everyone else had
gone home, you told me...
"What'd you think we will talk
about after becoming adults?"
Yeah! I remember that!
So how about this...
The one who pushed you
onto those train tracks...
...was me.
Eh?
You should've died back then.
But someone saved you.
It's Naoto Tachibana!
To me, it looks like he knew for sure
that you will fall onto the train tracks.
This might sounds crazy, but...
Are you perhaps...
able to return to the past?
And then you asked Tachibana Naoto
in the past to save you.
Isn't that right?
It would be weird if it isn't!
He shouldn't be able to save you there
if he hadn't known beforehand!
Right?! It's weird right?!
Stop it!
Who's the weird one here?!
What are you saying, Akkun?!
You're not like this!
You were always composed.
You can sacrifice yourself
for your friend's sake.
You were kind.
Dependable.
That's why...
You have to be lying!
There's no way Akkun would kill me!
Akkun is my friend!
Takemichi.
Just how did I end up like this?
I'm now of one of Kisaki's men.
Kisaki?
You mean Tetta Kisaki?
Everyone in Toman is controlled by Kisaki.
I haven't even seen Mikey-kun in years.
Akkun...
It's not too late!
You should just quit Toman!
No... that's impossible.
I'm scared.
I'm simply too scared of Kisaki.
Akkun...
Takemichi.
Mikey changed after Draken died.
Eh?
Draken is dead?!
He's not the type of person
who deserves to die.
Draken who shouldn't die, died.
And I'm here playing around
with filthy money.
I always admired you.
You always stand firm even while crying.
Akkun?
The person you want to save
by returning to the past...
It's "her," right?
It's dangerous.
Get down from there.
It sure is the "ultimate love," isn't it?
Good luck, Takemichi.
Please save everyone.
Akkun!
Our crybaby hero.
Stop it Akkun!
Akkun!
I'm sorry but please leave
him alone for now.
It's fine.
They want to ask me stuff, right?
Please don't force yourself.
Let's take a rest for a while.
Naoto.
Please investigate
Ken Ryuguji's death for me.
The man who turned Toman into
a crime organization is Tetta Kisaki.
Naoto...
I want to...
Draken... Akkun...
and Hina...
I want to save all of them!
I just want to be right next to you
Next to your slightly sweaty shirt
The rain falls all of the sudden
So I kissed you in that lonely night
If you look back, I will always
be there and smiling at you
Please
Give up on that unachievable future
Take it now
In the real new world
If I have to give you a name,
it's "My Hero"
That straight wish
Will go beyond the stopped time
"I don't need anyone but you"
I will keep living here
Break down that crooked needle
Shout out that firm words
Kick away that unmeaning destiny