Mikey, we're here.
What the hell you guys are here for?
Don't you dare to show
your face here! Get lost!
Who do you think you're talking to--
Hey, what are you doing?!
It's all our fault.
Just what did she even do to you guys?
We're going to fight Moebius soon.
The problem in our world is something
we must deal with ourselves.
All of our members have families
and people they care about.
You don't have to force yourself to bow.
Have a heart and care about others.
Sorry, Ken-chin.
I...
...am glad that you're here with me.
Can you call Pah-chin tomorrow?
Okay. I'll go get Peh, too.
In the warehouse near Second Mid, right?
I'm counting on you.
See you.
There is no way Mikey and Draken
will fight each other.
Draken died on August 3rd.
I must look up about Moebius before then!
We got our collars grabbed
and took an intense punch
After we got beaten up
Together we crouched
The anticipated rain came
"This should clean your bruise"
you lied with a smile
Even though you're bad at argument
So stop making such lame jokes
It's so bad I teared up
Getting blue bruises all the time
I cry, cry, and cry
Leaning our unstable heart together
We fight against the rotten Bad End
I wonder why
The pleasant pain was more vivid,
even more than the happiness
Clicking our tongue over our wet clothes
We look at each other's face and laugh
The Revenge we swore in that rainy night
I was born in the
red-light district in Shibuya.
I don't know who's my dad.
My mom's is a prostitute.
She left me when I was two.
I lived in "Fashion Health."
Sign here, okay?
Got it.
You sure are big now, Ken-bou.
I drink milk every day, after all.
Then see you again next time.
Kay~
Morning~
Thank you.
Thanks.
You should go to school now, Ken-bou.
Want a blowjob?
No need.
See you~
Yeah.
I was in fifth grade of elementary school.
I grew up surrounded by pink
towel and the smell of lotions.
Good morning!
Good morning, Ken-kun!
It's not "Ken," it's Draken.
Are you sure about this?
Of course.
Putting a tattoo on your temple
gonna hurt, you know?
Just do it fast.
Suit yourself.
I'll start now.
Shut it. You're a man, aren't you?
THAT HURT!!!
There, it's done.
So cool!
A tattoo at such a young age.
You're not gonna grow up
into a proper adult.
Thank you!
I'll show this off to everyone!
It will take a while before
your swell goes off.
Got it!
My body was bigger than
normal middle schooler.
I'm Ken Ryuguji from Fourth Elmn!
Draken!
If you see my dragon tattoo,
you better hide.
I was in fifth grade when
I had my dragon tattoo.
Even for middle schoolers,
there was hardly anyone dared to fight me.
Ken.
Aren't you being too
full of yourself lately?
You're picking too much fight
with middle schoolers.
Want us to beat you again?
I'm sorry.
They're the Samayama Gang
who ruled this area.
They once beat me up and left
me with only my pants on.
Not even I would dare to
fight them again ever since.
Speaking of not knowing his place,
there's a brat from Seventh Elmn.
Ah, you mean Mikey?
The one who got famous after
he beat Shino from Bachikan?
Ken.
Bring Mikey to us.
That brat is a lunatic!
Not even I feel like I can win against
a high schooler, much less a strong one.
If I bring him to them,
he wouldn't even stand a chance!
But before that,
I want to fight him first!
Hey!
You're from Seventh Elmn, right?
Y-Yeah?
I'm looking for this kid called
"Mikey," do you know him?
If you're looking for him,
then just now...
Ah! Mikey-kun!
What?
He's different from what I imagined!
I thought he would be a giant
monster who's bigger than me!
This guy's tiny!
He's just an ordinary brat!
He's coming!
What should I do?
Should I punch him?
Hey.
Don't you think the name
"Forty-eight tricks" is weird?
Eh?
No matter how you think about it,
there's barely a forty of it.
What do you think?
W-What do I think?
I never even heard of that.
Erm, you're Mikey, right?
Yeah, that's right.
What is it?
Some dudes from middle school
asked me to take you to them.
Huh?
Well...
I won't force you.
Okay!
Eh?
I'll come along because you asked me.
I'll go put my stuff at school first.
What a weird guy.
He gets me off the mood.
I bet this squirt will get beaten
up in no time.
Hey~
I brought him.
This guy's Mikey--
That moment...
Mikey ran straight towards Samayama...
And jumped.
You people couldn't do anything
unless you're in a pack.
What do you want?
I'm the great Mikey from Seventh Elmn.
Incredible!
You're Draken from Fourth Elmn, right?
Why a cool kid like you hanging
out with scum like them?
You should be my friend.
Ken-chin.
Are you sure Osanai is here, Naoto?
You got back all of the sudden
and asked me to investigate.
You think I have enough
time to fact check?
Sorry about that.
It's an emergency.
Huh?
And that info you gave me about Mikey-kun
and Draken-kun fighting was total bunk!
There is absolutely no way
those two would fight each other.
And instead, a battle between Toman
and Moebius is about to begin in the past.
So Ryuguji would die in that dispute.
Yeah.
That's why if we can learn about
the dispute from Osanai here,
we might be able to find a clue
on how to prevent Draken's death.
Umm, excuse me.
Can you please let me through?
Ah, I'm sorry.
Thank you, I'm sorry.
But you sure are one hell of a cop, Naoto.
Please be vigilant, okay?
You're late, Osanai!
Eh?
Osanai?
Why are you taking leisure time eating?!
But I came back on time...
If you can't do your job well,
you should at least
work more than others!
That guy is Osanai?
The former president of Moebius?
You sure this isn't some mistake?
Let's try asking him.
Umm...
Did I do something?
No.
We're investigating the Tokyo Manji
Gang incident from a few days ago.
12 years ago,
as the president of Moebius,
you started a dispute with
the Tokyo Maji Gang, right?
Can you tell us--
I have nothing to talk about.
You were involved in Ken Ryuguji's death.
No, that is...
A member of Moebius stabbed him.
No.
It was your order to kill him, wasn't it?
No!
It's true.
We did fight Toman.
But it wasn't us who killed him.
That was merely the trigger.
That man started an infight in Toman.
Eh?
Then, on August 3rd...
Draken died.
All of that was part of that man's scheme.
That man?
I'm sorry.
I can't tell you any more than this.
I don't want to get involved with Toman.
I'm sorry.
My boss will yell at me
I'll be going now.
I'm sorry for taking your time.
T-Thank you!
If only Draken hadn't die...
Then I...
What do you think?
Seeing how frightened he looks,
it doesn't seem like he's lying to us.
If we take his words at face value,
then the fight with Moebius
is nothing but the trigger.
According to him, someone was
plotting to start an infight in Toman.
And Osanai was being used for that.
That means...
there was someone who wanted to
make Draken and Mikey fight each other?
Why would anyone...
Anyway, the dispute with
Moebius was the start of it all.
That means Toman must not fight Moebius.
We must stop them!
Yes.
Please tell Mikey about this.
Yeah, I'll try to convince him.
Yamagishi is always like that.
He farted right when it was getting good.
He always makes trouble, doesn't he?
What's wrong, Takemichi?
Akkun!
Please save everyone.
Our crybaby hero.
Hey, Takemichi!
Sorry, I wasn't listening.
Safe!
Hey, what are you laughing?!
I see!
He's still alive!
Also, you didn't listen
to me again, did you?
Your front! Front!
Akkun.
Akkun, do you have a dream?
Why are you acting so
"adolescent" all of the sudden?
Just tell me.
My dream?
To be a beautician, I guess?
You should become one.
What are you talking about?
I'm not even sure of it yet.
You will definately become one!
C'mon, stop that.
What's wrong with you, Takemichi?
I'll be cheering for you.
So you better become one.
O-Okay...
Akkun, I must go now.
Eh? Where are you going?
It's an urgent matter.
I will be you first customer.
O-Okay...
Great! It's a promise, okay?!
Then see you tomorrow.
I want to save Akkun.
I want to save Draken.
I want to save Hina.
I must stop the dispute with Moebius!
Mikey-kun!
No matter what, I will stop it!
What is it, Takemicchi?
Why are you here?
You again?
Get lost, shithead!
Sorry, but we're having
an important discussion here.
Can you stop this fight with Moebius?
Huh?
I can't tell you why, but there's
someone pulling the strings here.
That hurt...
You really should stop goofing around.
Isn't that so, Pah-chin?
Get lost.
One more word and you're dead.
I understand, Draken.
I won't start off on my own.
So how should we attack them?
You can't!
You guys must not fight Moebius.
Toman will get trapped.
Get up.
We can't fight and you can't say why?!
Then who the hell beat my friend
and raped his girlfriend?!
I don't know!
But...!
Takemicchi.
I get what you're saying.
We will fight Moebius.
You don't understand at all.
I've decided that we're gonna fight.
So Toman's gonna fight Moebius.
I can't back off!
If you guys fight Moebius,
Toman is done for!
Just when I finally become friends
with Mikey-kun and Draken-kun!
I don't want Toman to end like this!
You're really a moron!
What are you doing, Draken?
Takemicchi said he won't back off.
Maybe it's not a bad idea to first
see what Moebius is all about.
Mikey.
Huh?
Ken-chin, are you defying Toman?
That's not what this is about.
Yes it is.
Sorry to interrupt your
little group implosion.
Moebius that, Moebius this.
Could you please stop yelling
our name so many times?
You mid-school babies.
You are... Osanai!
(8th President of Moebius - Nobutaka Osanai)
Shut it, dick cheese.
Eh?
That Osanai?!
You bastard...!
Hey, I'm two years older than you.
That's Mr. Bastard to you.
Yub, nothing but a middle schooler punk.
Tokyo Manji Gang?
You should change your name.
To "Mid-School Infaint Alliance."
I heard you guys were planning
to pick a fight with Moebius.
So we come to you ourselves.
-Let's do this.
-Dance, mid-schoolers.
Look, they're so scrawny.
Mikey-chan!
We're surrounded?!
This is war.
Anyway, the dispute with
Moebius was the start of it all.
That means Toman must not fight Moebius.
We must stop them!
This is bad, what should I do?
I just want to be right next to you
Next to your slightly sweaty shirt
The rain falls all of the sudden
So I kissed you on that lonely night
If you look back, I will always
be there and smiling at you
Please
Give up on that unachievable future
Take it now
In the real new world
If I have to give you a name,
it's "My Hero"
That straight wish
Will go beyond the stopped time
"I don't need anyone but you"
I will keep living here
Break down that crooked needle
Shout out that firm words
Kick away that unmeaning destiny