The embassy from Animal
Kingdom of Eurazania sent
by the Demon Lord Carrion
has arrived in Tempest.
But, a lot happened right
after they arrived...
...and it ended up like this.
Well, it's partly my fault, to be honest.
Let's give a name to a nameless flower
So that it won't freeze
from the coldness of solitude
If it's as frail as it is beautiful
Then it's not as fragile anymore
Like how you paint color
on a transparent body
Beyond the page of the chapter
It's welcoming you with a smile
Whenever, as much as it takes
Let's start a new world
We're Storyteller
All the love, hope, envy
Even the song of despair we sing today
It will all be a seed and bloom,
into a strong person
Why does salvation
born from someone's tear
That's just sad
Ideal and fantasy,
all mixed up by youthful impulse
My real self, is now reborn!
(Episode 26: The Trades with
the Animal Kingdom)
Is that all of Kijin's power?
Entertain me more!
That's my intention!
Prepare yourself!
That is?!
A giant Magic Shot?!
Hey, Shion! Wait!
Are you planning to blow
this whole area away?!
Crap, she's not listening.
Oh, nice! Come at me!
That Suphia girl seems to be
excited to take it straight on,
but not even she would make
it out unscratched against that!
What should I do?
Should I stop them?
Take this--
That's it!
It should be enough.
"Beast Transformation," huh...
Let's end it here.
So, did we pass?
Yes.
Then it's over.
M-Mister, what does that mean?
Seems like they were testing us.
We have no complaint.
You guys are pretty strong.
You all have the right to stand
on equal footing against us.
You guys have convinced me of that.
I hereby declare that we will now treat
the ruler of Jura Tempest Kingdom,
Rimuru Tempest and his friends
on the same level as Great Carrion.
You got it?
Yes, ma'am!
Like what Lady Suphia just said.
It's rare to meet a human like you
who could fight one on one against me.
It's my honor.
I was worried what would happen
right off the bat, but...
Good thing it all ended well.
Shion, you understand right?
Shion?
Well...
What should I do about this?
What?! It's about to explode?!
Can't you shut it off?
I can't! I'm at my limit already!
Great Rimuru, please evacuate.
C-Calm down!
Slowly, try to slowly
point that upward, okay?
U-Upward..?
Spirit! Push it with your spirit!
I don't think I can do it!
Oh well, that's Shion for you.
Shion, shoot it.
It's gonna be okay.
But...
Believe in me!
Okay! Here I go!
Gluttony!
There, it's over.
Impressive.
Seriously?!
It is to be expected from My Master.
Are you okay?
As expected from the man
acknowledged by Great Carrion.
It's a blessing to be able to
form a bond with you and your country.
Same goes for us.
Welcome to Tempest.
And thus, we welcomed
the envoy from Eurazania.
That night.
We held a modest welcome party
in the newly built Guest House.
This is great.
It's seasoned perfectly.
It got the right amount of salt.
I can eat these all day!
Delicious!
What a bliss.
She sure drinks a lot.
Just who the heck gave
her an entire barrel?
Meanwhile...
Is it okay for you guys to
show others that form?
It's not like it's a secret or anything.
I-I see...
But still...
We only show this form in
front of people we trust.
I see.
Oh well.
But still...
To think you would drink this
much of our apple brandy.
"This much"?
You don't make a lot of these?
Ah, sorry. Please, don't mind it.
We made those for the guests, after all.
But we rely on what the forest has
for us, so we couldn't make much of it.
Then I have a nice idea.
We have plenty of fruits
in Eurazania.
I'll have our men to deliver
some of it to you.
Really? Are you sure?
Yes.
Isn't that great, Great Rimuru?
Yeah!
I see.
So they want us to pass
some of the goods to them.
How about the rates?
I'll leave the details up to you.
I'm fine with anything as long as
I get to drink nice things.
Fruits from Eurazania are of a high quality,
so you can some expect good stuff.
So they want us to work
on the numbers ourselves.
What would be the right rate
for exchange of goods?
Oh well, let's leave it to
the professional.
Shuna.
What is it, Great Rimuru?
Call Koby for me.
He's a Kobold merchant.
(Kobold merchant - Koby)
He opens a shop here in Tempest and is
currently handling the merchant affairs here.
G-Great Rimuru, what do you need me for?
He's Koby, our merchants representative.
He used to do trades in
Demon Lord domain.
I'm appointing him to work
on the deals with you guys.
These two are the envoy
from the Animal Kingdom.
Please bring up stuff other than alcohol
that they might be interested in.
B-But the people of weak race are
not allowed to enter the Animal Kingdom--
I'll issue you a permit pass,
so feel free to come in.
I will also talk to Great Carrion
about you.
You look like a beastman anyway,
so I bet you will get along with them.
Anyway, I'm leaving it to you.
Well... ermm...
Okay.
I'll leave the rest to you young'uns.
Please excuse us.
Wha-, wait...
Great Rimuru!
Koby should be able to do it well.
Yes, you're right.
These kinds of stuff surprisingly go
smoothly with alcohol on the table.
And so, we all enjoyed
the party all night.
Things seem to go off smoothly for
our first formal meeting with another country.
Several days later.
Albis and Suphia returned to Eurazania.
We agreed to expand our
technology exchange.
These people remained in Tempest
to learn about our technology.
They're a diligent and kind bunch.
Just how does hot water come
out from this "faucet" thingy?
It doesn't look like it gets
boiled elsewhere.
It's Rune magic.
Rune magic?
Where did you put the Rune?
We engraved a Rune with heat magic
on the faucet handle.
I see.
So it will heat the water
when someone with magic turns it.
As expected from a Dwarf craftsman.
Well, this is nothing much.
It came from Mr.Rimuru's idea, after all.
(To be precise, it's Great Sage's idea.)
You're not going to look around
like the other guys?
It's not my duty.
The "Panther Fang" Phobio is
under a house arrest now,
and he told me to do something
useful for Lord Rimuru.
So that's why you join the town
security, huh?
Indeed so.
Grucius!
It's time for patrol.
Okay!
See you.
I guess I'll go take a bath
or something.
You got a sword training to do.
Yes.
As for fractional division,
it's a bit hard to calculate it
as it is,
so lets try to turn it into multiplication
and start from there.
To turn division into multiplication...
They're taking the class properly
even without me.
And then, more days passed.
Youm and his gang resume
their journey as a Champion.
And on the same day, Benimaru and
the rest of the embassy returned.
The Eurazania knights were as expected.
Each of them received proper training
from the Demon Lord Carrion himself.
To be expected from a Beastmaster, I guess.
Anything else?
Yes.
Their architecture is not much
compared to the one in Tempest.
However, their royal palace was
stuffed with luxuries
showing their remarkable
obsession with wealth concentration.
Riguru is doing so great!
Well, anyway...
However, it was not a bad thing
for them.
The residents actually wished for it.
I see.
Our architecture and crafts are on
a level above theirs.
In addition to Kaijin, we got Kurobei
and Shuna after all.
However, they have one thing that
is worth paying attention to.
And that is?
Their agriculture.
Oho!
They possess big fields that are
bigger than our whole country
and it's filled with colorful corps.
Can we learn anything from them?
I believe it's possible.
Great!
We will have the next embassy
to focus on their agriculture.
The food situation in our country
has improved a lot,
however, we still have a lot
of trails and errors to go through.
As such, this might lead to further
improvement on the situation--
Riguru is so--
Well then, I got to prepare for the trip
to the Dwarf kingdom.
So I'll leave the rest to you guys.
I'm counting on you.
Yes, sir!
Great Rimuru.
If it is possible, could you appoint Riguru
as the head of the next embassy?
What do you mean?
I believe Demon Lord Carrion
is a man worthy of our trust.
They won't treat our emissary
in a rough manner.
Thus, it should be wise for me to
stay here and protect the country instead.
I see.
So you're saying that it should
be okay to leave the rest to Riguru, right?
Yes.
Got it. Then it's done.
Thank you very much.
But to think that you would
trust him this much.
Carrion must be a great king,
beyond his prowess.
Indeed.
The truth is, I tried to pick a fight
with him, but he laughed it off.
Wait, what did you...?
I couldn't use big moves like Hell Flare,
so they took me down pretty easily.
I still have long to go.
Oh my...
Ah, but I won against Phobio.
I see...
Well, it sure is amazing that
you won against Phobio...
No good. As I thought, it was
wrong to let this guy go outside.
So after this and that...
The following day.
This time, I departed to Dwargon.
Hey, Ranga! Too fast!
Yes! Understood!
Ranga!
This time, we got Gobuta, Gobuzo, and
all six of Goblin Rider to accompany us.
Shuna and Shion.
And then, Kaijin, and Garm, Dord, and Myrd,
the three Dwarf brothers.
We're happy to be given the opportunity to go
and relax in Dwargon after such a long time.
It's true. You guys think so too, right?
Indeed!
I'm happy that you guys feel like that.
Our country got this far thanks
to you guys, after all.
As a craftsman, it's really
a wonderful word to hear.
Yeah.
We're really lucky to meet you guys.
Mister!
By the way, we got the presents for King
Gazel packed on the two carriages behind us.
It would've been much easier to just
pack it all inside my stomach, but...
The modus is also important
in such occasion.
She scolded me.
As expected from the Ogre princess.
She learned stuff from Vesta recently,
and is now quite knowledgeable in manners.
By the way, it would've much better
to leave Shuna behind, but...
Princess Shuna and Great Rimuru
will go on a trip together?
No, it's not a trip. It's for a job.
That's unfair! Unfair!
It's unfair that only Princess Shuna
gets to play with Great Rimuru--
A job, okay? It's a job...
Ms.Shion is mad!
Please calm down!
Well, she would cry, scream,
and rage and all...
So, can I leave her in your care, Rigurd?
T-This is nothing...
I'm worried about Rigurd and others if
I left Shion behind, so I took her with me.
Well, she got the looks of a skilled secretary
as long as she keeps her mouth shut.
Everything should go well
if I keep watching on her.
Great Rimuru, look.
The road that got destroyed
during the battle with Charybdis
has been mostly fixed.
You're right. They sure work fast.
As expected from the Orcs.
Right according to the plan.
Sir Geld, we need more cobblestone.
Got it.
I'll contact the people
at the quarry later.
Thank you.
That is...?
So today's the day of your departure
to the Dwarf kingdom?
Yeah.
You guys fixed the road,
so it's been a nice ride for us.
Thank you.
We worked on the road from
the Dwarf kingdom area.
So everything from here on
is a completed street.
Looks like it will just gets
better for us.
Good job.
Thank you very much.
So.
This is...?
A beer.
Beer?!
Don't drink too much, okay?
Yes, sir!
And so, the trip went smoothly.
Four days after the departure.
We arrived in the Armed Nation of Dwargon.
Open the gate!
They've got such imposing demon beasts,
are they someone important?
Are those even a demon beasts?
I've never seen it.
Their carriages seem to be made
with unique technology.
Hey, Brother.
Looks like you're doing well.
Kaido!
Long time no see!
How are you doing?
I'm having fun working for Mister Rimuru.
I bet so.
I can tell just by looking.
How about you guys?
Thanks to you.
Yeah.
So.
Where's Mr.Rimuru?
He's the state guest, after all.
I better greet him first.
What is he talking about?
I'm here...
Ah, I see.
He only knew me in my slime form.
This is him.
Him.
Well, a lot happened.
Mr.Rimuru... I'm glad that
you're doing well...
Ermm... well, please, over here.
Well, that's to be expected.
And so, we safely get into Dwargon
and are now heading to meet King Gazel.
I'm glad that you're doing well,
Mr.Rimuru.
Same goes to you, Mr.Dorf.
You can drop the formalities with me.
Well then.
Our king is waiting for you.
He's Dorf, the Leader of the Pegasus Knights
who assisted us during the fight with Charybdis.
Pegasus Knights are the king's
top-secret unit,
so he usually disguises himself
as a civil servant like this.
The ruler of Jura Tempest Federation,
Rimuru Majesty has arrived!
Please, come in.
The king of the Armed Nation of Dwargon,
Gazel Dwargon.
Long time no see, Rimuru.
I see.
Thanks for the work.
It was a very intriguing report.
Thank you.
I don't mind returning your
heart at this point.
But it would be great if you could do
one more work for us.
What do you need me to do?
Great Clayman.
It's nothing big.
It's a very simple thing, in fact.
Mjurran.
I'm used to losing things
I said it like it's someone else's problem
It's a blurry realism
Because it's not about me
The nameless sadness disappears,
warped in a legato-like dream
Will we feel better if we hug each other?
The life which I repeat is a joined miracle
Don't forget me, pass your voice to me
If I were to live for someone's sake
I wish that someone is you
(I'll tell you one more story)
If I can redo this world once again
I will paint that story with love
You'll know how this story's gonna end
I will tell you
I will tell you one more story
You'll know how this story's gonna end
I will tell you
Next time,
"Heaven, Once Again."