And so, we finally arrived in
Armed Nation of Dwargon.
Today we're here to meet the king of Dwarf,
Gazel Dwargo.
Let's give a name to a nameless flower
So that it won't freeze
from the coldness of solitude
If it's as frail as it is beautiful
Then it's not as fragile anymore
Like how you paint color
on a transparent body
Beyond the page of the chapter
It's welcoming you with a smile
Whenever, as much as it takes
Let's start a new world
We're Storyteller
All the love, hope, envy
Even the song of despair we sing today
It will all be a seed and bloom,
into a strong person
Why does salvation
born from someone's tear
That's just sad
Ideal and fantasy,
all mixed up by youthful impulse
My real self, is now reborn!
(Episode 27: Paradise, Once Again)
First, I would like to express
my thank to you.
Thank you very much for
helping Kaijin and the brothers.
Exiling them from here was the best
way to convince the ministers, after all.
So you were planning to forgive
them from the beginning?
I figured it also won't be good to let someone
as suspicious as you roaming in the country.
But still, it was a hard decision
to let Kaijin and the brothers go.
We were able to produce armor
thanks to Garm.
Dord and Myrd were helping
a lot with construction.
Also, Kaijin helped out
in fields that I'm not good at.
So we managed to work
as a group somehow.
They couldn't do much over here, after all.
It was for the best to have them
go and use their talents elsewhere.
What about Vesta?
Is he not here?
Well, I did invite him, but...
Hmm...
Thank you for the offer, but
I don't think I can show myself
in front of King Gazel before
I accomplish anything yet.
That's what he said.
That's just like him.
Then that means he too has finally found
a place where he can use his talent well.
So, Rimuru.
There's something I need
to confirm from you.
Yes.
I'm also here for that matter.
The thing that defeated Charybdis...
Just what is this so-called
high-power magic weapon?
I heard it has the unprecedented power
that surpasses even a strategy class magic.
Actually, that really was the power
of Demon Lord Milim.
Demon Lord Milim?
He did say such a joke that day.
But it's not joke, actually...
I'm sorry, but it's hard to believe.
That girl...
Yaaay~!
...That Catastrophe class Demon Lord?
Well, I get why you can't believe me.
It's too absurd even for a tall tale.
Very well. I will believe you, Rimuru.
You get that, Dorf?
Yes.
However...
To think that you managed to
befriend the ancient Demon Lord.
You're truly a man full of wonder.
Why does she look so proud?
I apologize for the wait.
What's that?
Well, a little present from me.
Please enjoy.
For you too, Lord Dorf.
Thank you.
This is...
Did Dord made this?
Precisely.
It's excellent.
What a thin and fine symbol.
Is this Rune magic for detoxification?
How nice of you.
I won't mind tasting for poison
if you like, though.
I wouldn't expect you
trying to poison me anyway.
This is a fine wine.
This is...!
Delicious.
It's wonderful.
Then, me too.
Delicious!
Warning.
Poison Resistance.
Succeed.
Don't do that!
What's the point of wine
without the alcohol!
What's wrong?
Ah, well, it's nothing.
This is a distilled liquor
made from apple.
We just secured an import of fruits,
so I believe we can mass
produce this someday.
Import?
So you mean you've made a connection
with a country other than Dwargon?
Is it with the Kingdom of Blumund?
Yeah, that too.
But the fruits will be from
the Animal Kingdom--
Is it Eurazania?!
Y-Yeah.
The prideful beast king is
doing trades with other countries?!
So not only with Demon Lord Milim,
you also befriend Demon Lord Carrion?
What a fearsome seducer
of Demon Lords...
No, no, no.
I just happened to help one of
Demon Lord Carrion's men.
So from there, we agreed to
do trades with each other.
Well, we're still just sending
out embassy the other day.
Even so, now Tempest will become
the new center of attention.
It might eventually replace Falmuth as
the new main place for foreign trades.
Indeed.
You're overestimating me.
For now, we still have to secure a safe
transportation route to do trades and all.
That matter aside,
what I'm drinking right now is
better than any I've got from Falmuth.
I'm expecting great result from you.
The Kingdom of Falmuth, huh...
That's the name of Youm's
hometown, wasn't it?
Got cold?
Sheesh, seems like someone
out there is talking about me.
I don't think I've heard him
talking about his hometown.
What kind of country is this
Kingdom of Falmuth, anyway?
Well, they're one of the biggest
country out there in the west.
Most of our foods are imports from
Falmuth and the Empire.
However...
Just between you and me.
I don't like that king.
Really?
That king is too greedy.
That's why you must secure that
deal with Eurazania no matter what.
And then, you better share some
drinks to your senior, okay?
You being my senior has nothing
to do with this, right?
It will be all okay~!
Ah! Shion! When did you start drinking?
I'm sure Great Rimuru will make the deal
with Eurazania a success wonderfully!
Hey!
Then delicious food will start lining
on our table every day!
If you put delicious wine on top of it,
then it's practically a sealed deal already!
Just leave everything to Great Rimuru!
Safe!
Sheesh, this girl is just so hopeless...
I'm sorry you had to witness that.
Sorry for what my secretary just did.
It's okay.
Just go take her to her room.
W-Well then, please excuse us.
That was so embarrassing.
Yeah, it sure was.
Great Rimuru...
But still, it makes me want to live
up to her expectation.
Shuna, let's check the script again
once we get to our room!
Yes!
The next day.
Today is the day Dwargon and Tempest
will announce their friendship treaty.
This is the place for us to appeal to
the people that we're a good friend.
In other words, I'm standing here
representing the whole image of Tempest.
I better give a proper greeting
and leave a good impression.
NICE TO MEET YOU, EVERYONE!
I'm Rimuru Tempest, the ruler of Jura
Tempest Federation, Tempest in short.
Ah, thank you, thank you!
Ahem.
I'm wishing to build a country that serves
as the bridge between monster and human.
Dwargon is a place of coexistence and
co-prosperity between human and monster.
And it is what I'm striving to make.
I can't thank King Gazel enough
for supporting my ideal.
I hope we can build a relationship
where we can help each other.
For that, I need the help
from each and every one of you.
There are a lot of monsters,
including me who lives in Tempest.
It truly is a country of monsters.
However, what we hold dear is
no different from everyone here.
If possible, as opposed to fearing us
because we're monsters,
I want you to welcome us as a new friend.
I promise you that these words
are coming from my heart.
This has been my greeting to all of you.
Great Rimuru!
It was not bad of a speech, I must say.
Too short, too humble, too much appeal.
To be frank, it was terrible.
As a king who rules over a country,
you shouldn't act so humble to the people.
Moreover, you will only get yourself looked
down upon by residents from other countries.
Mere wishful thinking is no good
in regard to governance.
Truly great thing doesn't come naturally.
It's something you must
work hard to get.
Yes...
Even back as a salaryman, I'm bad
at doing morning speech, wasn't I?
But still, he's undoubtedly saying
all of these for my sake.
I'm truly blessed with the people I meet.
I must be thankful for that.
We somehow managed to get
through the big event in Dwargon.
That's why, it shouldn't be wrong
to have fun at times like these.
Yes, now that I'm in Dwargon...
There's that place that I can't
possibly forget!
This is the Butterflies of the Night!
The elven paradise!
Gobta, you made sure that
Shuna and Shion didn't notice, right?
Of course!
Okay!
Let's go to the promised land!
Yes, sir!
Welcome.
We were waiting for you, Little slime.
I'm here, in paradise!
Erofu!
Ah, I mean elf ladies!
Are you doing great?
Of course.
Hey, me first, okay?
It's here!
He's bouncing.
I'm bouncing~
It has been long.
We thought you forgot about us already.
Of course not~
Really?
Really!
Welcome, young boys.
You must be Mr.Slime's friends.
Welcome here.
I will be in your care!
Well, what "care" would that be?
I love you.
Oh my, I'm flattered.
Gobta sure does crazy stuff sometimes.
She let it slide just like that, though.
Your companion is already here.
Rimuru, I'm glad that you invite me too.
You helped me a lot, after all.
Please let me do this much.
That form does suit you the best.
You don't like my humanoid form?
Well, it's not really about that.
It just doesn't fit my impression of you.
Well, it can't be helped.
You should have fun talking with
your brother tonight.
Don't be stupid!
Why should we talk to dudes
in a place like this?
We got pretty ladies here,
so let's have all the fun we can get!
He's right, Rimuru.
It's rude to say that here.
Ah, these brothers do
resemble each other.
Wow, Gobta!
You're so good!
Is that so~?
This is piece of cake for me!
Hey, that's dangerous.
That glass is very expensive.
So you better not drop it, okay?
So meany~!
And if you drop it...
Let's see...
We will have you pay for it
with your body, I guess?
It's just a joke, okay?
Manager, can you have a second?
What is it, Little slime?
If you don't mind, would you
have this for the store?
What's this?
It's a new wine product we made.
I'm also giving these to King Gazel,
so I can't give out a lot.
But please try serving it
to some loyal customers.
I want to hear some feedback.
Oh my.
But are you sure?
I want you to check out how much
we can sell for a glass of this.
Oh my.
You sure are diligent, Little slime.
You're like a completely different person
compared to when you give a speech back then.
Eh, you were watching?!
With my eyes wide open.
W-Well, that... was just an act.
I looked innocent, right?
I will take your word for that.
But still, I got a good impression of you.
Eh?
You looked so sincere.
I believe sincerity is the key
to attract people.
In that regard, I give you a full score.
I also want to see it.
A country where human, monster, elf,
and all other races can smile together.
Thank you.
And thus, we end our night with joy.
Hey, get hang of yourself, Kaijin.
You drink too much.
Yeah, you're right.
What a bunch of drunkard.
And Gobta got anemia.
Hey, Gobta, are you okay?
My eyes are spinning...
Sheesh.
You all better avoid getting found
by anyone on your way back to the inn.
What we experience tonight
is our secret, okay?
Yes!
C'mon, let's go.
Do you need a help?
Ah, thank you--
Sh-Sh-Shu--
Warning. Tremendous energy
detected behind that smile.
Ah, I can see it too.
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Why--
"Why are you here?" you ask?
Gobzo told me everything.
Gobzo, why?!
Eh? Princess Shuna asked where I'm
going, so I just answered her.
What the heck did you just do?!
How awful of you, Great Rimuru...
It was awful of you to leave me like that.
Eh, but, well, that's...
Why did you go off
without telling me?
So it's you guys who invited
Great Rimuru to go on a night out?
I have no intention to stop you from
doing the thing you want.
It's just you made us a tiny bit lonely.
Ugh...
Well--
Excuses will only worsen the situation.
I just have to be honest here.
I'm sorry!
Lower myself.
I won't do it again!
Then appeal to their emotion
with my slime cuteness!
Okay?
I understand.
Phew.
I will let you off the hook with
one week of Shion's morning meal.
Thank--
Eeh?!
Are you sure, Princess Shuna?
Yes.
Do your best, Shion.
Yes, I will do my best!
Too short, too humble, too much appeal.
King Gazel, what you said was right.
E-Erm...
Can you shorten it to three days?
One week.
Okay...
And thus, we finished
all our business in Dwargon
and are now on our way back home.
Ah!
There he is, Miss.
He's Youm, the Champion.
Hey, Issac. What is it?
This miss over here wants to talk
to you, so can you help her out?
Miss?
I'm good at magic, so I believe
I can be helpful for a Champion like you.
I heard there aren't much
magic-user in your group.
That's a shame.
We have enough of magic user.
Just what can a woman do, anyway?
Then I'll show you just how fearsome
a real Wizard can be.
What?!
Earth Lock.
I can't move!
She used such a simple magic like that?!
Air Shot!
I will beat you down!
It's over.
I'm shocked.
You didn't have any single
countermeasure against status effect.
How are you supposed to fight
a magic user like that?
You beat me.
You sure are strong.
What's your name?
Mjurran.
Nice to meet you, Mjurran.
I'm used to losing things
I said it like it's someone else's problem
It's a blurry realism
Because it's not about me
The nameless sadness disappears,
warped in a legato-like dream
Will we feel better if we hug each other?
The life which I repeat is a joined miracle
Don't forget me, pass your voice to me
If I were to live for someone's sake
I wish that someone is you
(I'll tell you one more story)
If I can redo this world once again
I will paint that story with love
You'll know how this story's gonna end
I will tell you
I will tell you one more story
You'll know how this story's gonna end
I will tell you
Next time, "The Falmuth Kingdom Scheme."