Demon Lord Clayman is known
as the "Marionette Master."
He rules over his subordinate like puppets.
That includes me.
My duty was to investigate Tempest.
I used Youm to infiltrate this town.
And under Clayman's order, I cast
that great magic, Anti-Magic Area.
My heart was stolen by Clayman
using his secret spell, Marionette Heart.
Ever since, I have no choice
but to follow his order.
I see.
So he literally has the power
over your life and death.
So why would Clayman
meddle with our country?
He once told me...
"This finally gets interesting."
"There were some unexpected things,
but a great war will begin"
At first, I thought it's about
Demon Lord Milim's attack on Carrion.
But seems like he's referring to
the war between Falmuth and Tempest.
Clayman...
He manipulates his subordinates as
he likes and avoids getting his hand dirty.
What a nasty guy.
From the looks of it, she's a Wizard.
But in this Anti-Magic Area,
she's as weak as a regular person.
That means he tossed her away.
Mister, please forgive her!
I beg you too!
She had no choice but to
follow what Clayman told her to!
I will think about Mjurran's
treatment later.
Until then, I will have you
under arrest in this Guest House.
Understood.
We will assign a guard to watch her.
Mister...
Sorry, Youm.
My mind's still not clear now.
If you're worried, I don't
mind you accompanying her.
Would that be all for now?
Yes.
Then let's pay the wounded a visit.
Show me the way.
Yes, sir.
Let's give a name to a nameless flower
So that it won't freeze
from the coldness of solitude
If it's as frail as it is beautiful
Then it's not as fragile anymore
Like how you paint color
on a transparent body
Beyond the page of the chapter
It's welcoming you with a smile
Whenever, as much as it takes
Let's start a new world
We're Storyteller
All the love, hope, envy
Even the song of despair we sing today
It will all be a seed and bloom,
into a strong person
Why does salvation
born from someone's tear
That's just sad
Ideal and fantasy,
all mixed up by youthful impulse
My real self, is now reborn!
(Episode 32: Hope)
How's everyone?
Great Rimuru!
The potion won't work.
The effect got blocked by
a Space element skill.
Even if I heal them, the effect
won't reach their injury.
I see.
Great Rimuru...
Please don't worry about us.
Neither I nor my incompetent disciple
is weak enough to die from this.
I'm not worried in the slightest.
Come on, show me your wound.
Great Sage.
The effects of the Space element
have been confirmed.
Use Gluttony to eat its effect?
Yes, of course.
Eh?
I'm saved?
Amazing, Great Rimuru.
Thank goodness!
Great Rimuru, welcome back!
H-Hey, Gobta!
Oh! You're fine, too, Geezer?
Do you want to sleep once again?
M-Master! I'm glad you're all fine!
That's why, please wait!
Ah, by the way, where's Shion?
She didn't go off on her own
for revenge, didn't she?
Actually, she might really do that, huh?
W-Well...
Great Rimuru...
Benimaru only said one thing.
"Please follow me."
And headed towards the plaza
where the dead bodies were enshrined.
...Gobzo?
Gobzo!
Shion protected a child who
was targeted by the attacker.
But she wasn't able to move as
she wanted because of the barrier.
Gobzo protected me.
The attacker just laughed at him,
and then...
Great Rimuru!
My bad.
Can you guys leave me
alone for a while?
Understood.
Come on.
Please call us anytime.
We will come right away.
Warning.
Powerful aura will put weakened
monsters under pressure.
Yeah...
I see.
I gave the Anti-Magic mask to Chloe.
Is the analysis done?
Complete.
Do you want to duplicate it?
Yes.
How did this happen?
Report. Incalculable.
Just what were we supposed to do?
Report. Unintelligible.
Was it a mistake to make contact
with human?
Report. Unanswerable.
Tell me. What did I do wrong?
Report. Incalculable.
Unintelligible.
Unanswerable.
My head is filled with strong emotion.
But at the same time, I'm extremely calm.
Not a single tears comes out.
Ah, I see...
My heart is already that of a monster.
Report.
No results found.
Failed to find any magic related
to a complete resurrection of the dead.
I see.
What about the barrier?
Report.
The analysis of the two barriers
covering the town is complete.
Removing the compound barrier is difficult.
But the Great Magic, Anti-Magic Area
can be removed.
Execute?
No. Not yet.
What I really want to remove
is this compound barrier.
But it sure has troublesome property.
I can't let them be like this forever.
Their dead bodies will eventually rot,
be reduced into magicule, and disappear.
At the very least, I can have them
sleep peacefully within me.
Rimuru!
So you came?
Please wait for a moment.
I need to put everyone to sleep now.
A-Actually!
The chances are slim.
Actually, there might not
even be a chance.
But there is a fairy tale about
resurrecting someone from the dead!
Fairy tell?
What the heck is that?
Why are you telling me that?
Stop it.
Don't give me hope.
You're telling me there is
more I can do for them?
For them?
No... that's not it.
I just don't want to lose them.
You might think it's just
some made-up stories,
but this one is based on real fact...
Rimuru?
Sorry for startling you.
I'm just happy.
Resurrection, huh.
It does sound like a fairy tale.
If the chance is not at zero,
it's worth a try.
Tell me more about it.
Eren.
The Western Holy Church groups
are camping near the town.
Each group is protecting
what looks like a magic device.
Looks like those devices are
what created the barrier.
Can you neutralize them?
I can take down at least one group.
Got it. You don't have to force yourself.
Just keep a watch on the surrounding area.
Yes.
Kept you waiting, Eren.
Tell me more about that
resurrection fairy tale.
Okay.
It's fine.
This is a fairy tale passed down in
the Sorcerous Dynasty of Thalion.
A story about a certain
girl and a dragon.
Her parents were a dragon and a human,
and she was raised as a Dragon Princess.
One day, her dragon father made
a small copy of himself
and gave it to his daughter to be her friend.
However...
The small dragon was killed by a king
who wanted to take over the Dragon Princess.
The girl grieved, mourned, and raged.
With the power she inherited from her father,
she killed the king, several hundred thousand
of his people, and finally his whole country.
After that, the girl evolved
into a Demon Lord,
and following that, the small dragon
was miraculously resurrected.
But...
The small dragon had already lost
its soul after its death.
It is now nothing but an evil monster
who would destroy everything on its path.
A Chaos Dragon.
The girl once again mourns, and seals
the dragon who was once her friend.
This tale was the start of the Dragon
Princess who now became a Demon Lord.
The story ends here.
She destroyed an entire country
and evolved into a Demon Lord.
Following that, the small dragon she
bonded with got resurrected.
It's true that monsters just
evolve out of nowhere.
Just giving them a name was
a huge deal for them.
But there's no point in resurrecting
them as soulless monsters.
This town is being surrounded
by a barrier, right?
If this barrier is also keeping
the souls of the dead inside...
Report.
The soul of dead monsters would usually
scatter and disappears.
However, there is a chance that
the compound barrier is stopping them.
(Probability of the souls remaining)
The probability for that is 3.14 percent.
As low as value of pi...
No, it's the opposite.
There is over three percent chance
they can be resurrected.
All I have to do is to evolve
into a Demon Lord.
Thank you for telling me that, Eren.
But are you sure?
You're basically telling me
to become a Demon Lord.
And also...
The truth is, my real name
is Eryune Grimwalt.
I'm a noble from the Sorcerous
Dynasty of Thalion.
So you're actually a noble lady?
The two of us left our country to serve
as Lady Eren's bodyguard on her trip.
Really?
We're sorry for keeping it a secret.
I always looked up to adventurers who
look so free, so I left my country.
But only a select few in Thalion
knows about that story I told you.
If you become a Demon Lord, people will
eventually finds out that I'm involved.
But that's okay!
I also want to save everyone
in this town.
I also can't accept what Falmuth and
Western Holy Church did here.
If that's what Lady Eryune wants,
as her bodyguards, I have no objection.
Me neither.
You have good comrades.
Makes me jealous.
Yeah.
If you need something from us,
just let us know.
You have done so much for us, after all.
This time it's our turn to help you.
Thank you.
To keep the monsters' soul
from dissipating,
I then put on the third barrier.
Just in case something were to happen.
Demon Lord, huh...
Report.
The individual Rimuru Tempest
has already obtained a Demon Lord Seed.
A Demon Lord Seed? What's that?
Answer.
The Demon Lord Seed refers to whether one
has the qualification to evolve into a Demon Lord
based on their magicule and possessed skills.
It was obtained from consuming
the Orc Disaster.
By fulfilling the requirement, you can
evolve into a "True Demon Lord."
Really?
So what's the requirement?
Guessing from the fairy tale,
nutrients are needed to germinate the seed.
(Germinate Seed) (Nutrients)
The nutrients would be a human's soul.
Over ten thousand worth of it is needed.
I see.
Great Rimuru.
What is it?
I just received a report from
the far recon.
The allied force of Falmuth and Western
Holy Church is heading towards Tempest.
Approximately twenty thousands of them.
Perfect timing.
Perfect... timing?
No, it's not a big deal.
Thank you for the report.
It's nothing.
Excuse me.
Well then.
Mjurran.
I've decided on your punishment.
I will have you dead.
Mister!
Please wait! Mjurran is just--
Grucius!
What are you doing, Youm?
Take Mjurran with you and get outta here!
Mjurran, let's go! Hurry--
I loved you, Youm.
You're the first man I've fallen
for in all my life.
Don't fall by a bad woman
again next time, okay?
Goodbye.
Mjurran!
Mister! I beg you! Stop it!
I will amend for her! I will do anything!
Good determination.
I will make up for it for
my whole life!
No way! No! Mjurran!
Okay, looks like it went well.
Eh? Why am I still alive?
I think you're dead for
about three seconds.
Well, I did say I will have you dead,
but I have no intention to kill you.
Report.
The individual Mjurran's pseudo-heart
successfully operates normally.
(Operates normally)
Great.
I learned about this
when I put on the third barrier.
Clayman is using the temporary heart he
put on Mjurran to wiretap her surrounding.
Wiretap?
This emits encrypted electronic signal
and delivers it to Clayman.
So to deceive him, I need to make
it looks like I just killed Mjurran.
I'm sorry for making
you guys go through this.
It's fine.
Then... what's this beat on my chest?
It's an artificial heart I made
based on your temporary heart.
And of course, there's no wiretap in it.
Now you're free.
Clayman can't do anything to you now.
Isn't that great, Mjurran?
There's nothing that binds you anymore!
Rimuru...
No, Great Rimuru.
No words can I use to express
my gratitude to you.
If you wish for my loyalty,
then I will gladly give it to you.
No, you don't have to.
But I want you to help me with something.
What would that be?
Just like how you just died and
back alive,
there's a chance we can resurrect
Shion and others.
...Can it be done?
It's still a matter of chance.
And I want to do everything I can
to boost that chance.
Will you help me?
Understood.
I will do my best to help.
Thank you.
So what do you plan to do
after we're done with that?
I finally get my freedom back.
But I don't mind being confined
for a short human lifespan.
Eh?
Does that mean...
I don't need your pity!
Besides, Youm's human. So he'll
live for like a hundred years or so.
After that is my turn.
What did you just said?!
You're really thinking about that,
you shitty werewolf?!
Hah? What did you just say,
you shitty human?!
- You hear me, I said "shitty werewolf"!
- By the way, Youm.
- I've got a favor to ask of you.
Ah, yes.
I will do anything for you.
Be the next king of Falmuth for me.
Oh yeah, just leave it to me!
Eh?
King?
So we will kill the Falmuth army along with
their king who is heading this way.
But of course, that would put
their people in a bind, right?
That's where you come in.
I want you to govern Falmuth as their
new king and form a relation with us.
You made it sounds easy.
But me? A king?
It's fine.
I will be a Demon Lord after this,
so you might as well join me.
Great Rimuru is asking you
because he trusts you.
I will help you too, so why
not try to live an eventful life?
Count me in, too.
I will be by your side
waiting for the time you die.
What?!
Got it. I will do it.
Just leave it to me.
Great!
Sorry for keeping you all waiting.
The meeting now starts.
Our topic for today is about our
approach towards humans from now on...
...and resurrection of Shion and others!
I'm used to losing things
I said it like it's someone else's problem
It's a blurry realism
Because it's not about me
The nameless sadness disappears,
warped in a legato-like dream
Will we feel better if we hug each other?
The life which I repeat is a joined miracle
Don't forget me, pass your voice to me
If I were to live for someone's sake
I wish that someone is you
(I'll tell you one more story)
If I can redo this world once again
I will paint that story with love
You'll know how this story's gonna end
I will tell you
I will tell you one more story
You'll know how this story's gonna end
I will tell you
Next time, "With Everything."